很多我的流行音乐总是告诉我观看比例
Many My pop always told me to watch the scales.
说的工作！总是会找到一种方法来欺骗工人
Said the work! will always find a way to cheat the workin' man.
我在1933年遇到麦克麦德
I met Mac McLeod in 1933,
我亲眼目睹了真正变化的代价
and I witnessed up close the price of real change.
先生们 女士们 进来 进来
Gentlemen, ladies, come in, come in.
请听
Listen, please.
听到我要说 好吧？
Hear what I have to say, all right?
这个价格削减了我...
This price cut pains me...
尽可能多的痛苦你
as much as it pains you.
随着市场的波动
With the market as volatile as it is,
一个费拉应该算自己幸运
a fella should count himself fortunate
以获得可观的工资
to garner a respectable wage
像我提供你 -
like I offer you-.
好吧？
All right?
是的 尊敬像地狱！
Yeah, respectable like hell!
是啊！
Yeah!
人不能每天靠美元生活
Man can't live on a dollar a day.
你答应我们三天一天
You promised us three a day,
你懂的
and you know it.
但是 不幸的是 好人
But, unfortunately, good man,
我的...我的手被绑
my... my hands are tied.
我们今天要做什么？
What are we gonna do today?
我们将继续到下一个字段是啊！
We'll just go on over to the next field. Yeah!
不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不幸的是 这也不会工作
Unfortunately, that won't work either.
这是Torgas山谷每个地区的价格
That's the rate for every field for the Torgas Valley.
现在你可以把它作为它或...
And now you can either take it as it is or...
离开
leave.
离开？我不能离开
Leave? I can't leave.
我花了几乎我的最后一刻 只是试着出去这里
I spent nearly my last dimes just to try and get out here.
不能离开
Can't leave.
- 对不起太可惜了
- I'm sorry. That's a pity.
但你可以哼或去上班
But you can either whine or go to work.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我们走吧搬出去
Let's go. Move out.
好吧 来吧 伙计我们开工吧
All right, come on, folks. Let's do this.
正如他们在大战中说的
As they said in the Great War,
“这是日光在De Banque
"It's daylight in De Banque,
一个ch子的儿子在沼泽里
the son of a bitch is in the swamp.
嘿 赞美你们全能的上帝你要做什么 整天睡觉？
Hey, praise ye to the God Almighty. What are you gonna do, sleep all day?"
好人 好人
Good people, good people.
我的人民 我的人民
My people, my people.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
哦 嘿 你一定是新兵
Oh, hey, you must be the new recruit.
你......嘿 这意味着你遇到了哈利
You... hey, that means you met Harry.
哈利说你还好 你没事吧
Harry says you're okay, you're okay.
它是什么？
What is it?
插口？
Jack?
呃 我是吉姆吉姆•诺兰
Uh, I'm Jim. Jim Nolan.
喜悦 让他进来
Joy, let him in.
你说诺兰 Nolan？你是Ray Nolan的孩子吗？
You say Nolan. Nolan? Are you Ray Nolan's kid'?
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
喜悦 你的礼貌在哪里？ - 嗯？是啊
Joy, where's your manners? - Huh? Yeah.
你为什么不邀请我们的新朋友在这里？
Why don't you invite our new friend in here?
- 哦 对不起 是的 - 在这里 很高兴见到你 吉姆
- Oh, I'm sorry, yeah. - Here, nice to meet you, Jim.
- 啊 - 名称的Mac
- Ah. - Name's Mac.
- 很高兴见到你 - 好吧
- Nice to meet you. - All right.
呃 喜欢不摇伤害太多
Uh, Joy don't shake. Hurts too much.
砸了他的手 - 是的 因为我得到了真正的好
Busted his hands. - Yeah, 'cause I got beat real good.
没错 我被铐在酒吧
That's right, I been handcuffed to a bar
并砸在头骨上
and smacked across the skull.
我得到了警察马殴打我的手
I gotten my hands stomped on by police horses.
我被打败了地狱 不是我 Mac？
I been beat to hell, ain't I, Mac?
- 当然有 喜悦 - 好吧 杰伊
- Sure have, Joy. - All right, Jay.
吉姆 对不起来吧 有一个座位
Jim, sorry. Come on, have a seat.
Ray Nolan的孩子 是吗？ - 是的
Ray Nolan's kid, huh? - Yeah.
听说他是全县最艰难的杯子
Heard he was the toughest mug in the whole county.
说他可以用双手舔五个警察
Say he could lick five cops with his bare hands.
是啊太糟糕了 他每次出去 他设法跑到六个 但...
Yeah. Too bad every time he went out, he managed to run into six, but...
嗯...让我们希望你有更多的意义
Well... let's hope you got more sense than that.
现在 这里是伊迪丝•马龙
Now, this here's Edith Malone.
她没事对她来说太难了
She's all right. Little too tough for her own good.
去地狱 苹果你可以叫我埃迪
Go to hell, Mac. You can call me Edie.
他只是疼痛 因为我比他有更长的时间
He's just sore because I been at this longer than he has,
我也更好
and I'm better at it, too.
- 也许 也许这样 - 嗯
- Maybe, maybe, maybe so. - Mm-hmm.
你已经遇到了乔 Joy是一个老的兽医 不是你 Joy？
You already met Joy. Joy's an old vet, ain't you, Joy?
太他妈正确了
Damn right.
我没有爬过
And I ain't ever crawled.
我曾经...我有没有打破？
Did I ever... did I ever break?
我曾经乞求停止吗？决不
Did I ever beg 'em to stop? Never.
我继续叫他们的母狗
I kept on callin' them sons of bitches
直到他们敲我冷 每一个死的时间
right until they knocked me cold, every damn time.
好吧 也许如果你把你的陷阱关闭
Well, maybe if you'd kept your trap shut,
他们不会敲那么多的你的头
they wouldn't have knocked that head of yours around so much
你可以保持一周的日子
and you could keep straight the days of the week.
好吧 不要让他开始
All right, don't get him started.
是的 他们是子的儿子 所以我告诉他们
Yeah, well, they were sons of bitches, and so I told 'em.
你知道 他们可能骑着我 把我扔在地上 直到土壤
You know, they may have rode me down, ground me into the din till the soil
是我的血 是红色 但我告诉他们他们是什么！
was red with my blood, but I told them what they were!
你肯定的 快乐是啊 对的
You sure did, Joy. Yeah, damn right.
嘿 让我给你一些咖啡只是在这里等一下
Hey, let me get you some coffee. Just wait here.
男人 我知道一周的哪一天
Man, I know what day of the week it is.
好吧 欢乐
All right, Joy.
谁生产货物？
Who produces the goods?
- 呃 工人做
- Uh, the workers do.
谁获得利润？
And who takes the profit?
- 老板和业主？
- The bosses and the owner?
什么权利'？他们不生产nothin'
By what right'? They don't produce nothin'.
他们有什么权利？喜悦！
What right do they have? Joy!
你听起来像是一匹两马的牧师在一匹马的城镇
You sound like a two-bit preacher in a one-horse town.
你会停止试图说服我们自己的人
Will you just stop trying to convince our own people
并单独留下可怜的男孩？
and leave the poor boy alone?
吉姆 来吧
Jim, come on.
喜悦 让他走
Joy, let him go.
- 我和你在一起 欢乐 - 好吧好吧 杰克
- I'm with you, Joy. - All right. Okay, Jack.
只是在头顶上打了太多次
Just been smacked over the head one too many times.
我们照顾他 尽量保持他的麻烦
We take care of him, try to keep him out of trouble.
那些你唯一的衣服？
Those the only clothes you got?
- 嗯 是的
- Uh, yeah.
- 是的 要给你一件服装
- Yeah, gonna have to get you a costume.
- 你是什么意思 服装？
- What do you mean, a costume?
-  Cig？ - 不 谢谢
- Cig? - No, thank you.
你有很好的时机 吉姆伟大 事实上
You got good timing, Jim. Great, in fact.
明天上午 我要去Torgas山谷
Tomorrow morning, I'm heading to the Torgas Valley
你和我一起来
and you're coming with me.
-  Torgas是什么？ - 苹果
- What's in Torgas? - Apples.
字段多汁像你不会相信
Fields of 'em. Succulent like you wouldn't believe.
成千上万的潮人出来的季节来挑选
Thousands of boomers come out for the season to pick 'em.
可怜的混蛋花了他们每一分钱的钱在那里
Poor bastards spend their every last dime gettin' out there.
一旦他们在那里 老板将工资削减一半
As soon as they're there, bosses slash the wages in half.
像这样的人会疯了 愤怒
Guys like that's gonna be mad, furious.
有没有没有他们可以做到
There ain't nothin' they can do about it.
这就是你和我进来的地方我们要快速解决这个工作
That's where you and me come in. We're gonna fix that job real quick.
- 我们要开始罢工
- We're gonna start a strike.
- 瞧 看看那个
- Well, look at that.
孩子们有一些大脑去与所有的布朗
Kid's got some brains to go with all that brawn.
那么 你说什么？你准备好选择一些苹果？
So, what do you say? You ready to pick some apples?
- 算我一个
- I'm in.
Jeez 男人 我的流行音乐曾经工作过这些领域
Jeez, man, my pops used to work those fields.
他说 不管码头是多么糟糕 在那里工作 更糟糕的工作领域
He said no matter how bad the docks were, working there, way worse working the field,
因为如果他们抓住你干扰的领域 他们会杀了你
because if they catch you interfering in the fields, they'll kill you.
没有人会停下来 - 你为什么认为我们要出去？
There's no one to stop 'em. - Why do you think we're going out there?
要更改所有...
To change all that...
一次一个字段 如果我们必须
one field at a time, if we have to.
真正的问题是 你曾经跳过一列火车吗？
Real question is, have you ever jumped a train before?
- 我有过什么吗？跳了火车？ - 是的！
- Have I ever what? Jumped a train? - Yeah!
你知道 我从来没有出过这个城市
You know, I never been out of the city before.
妈的 这不是一个景象我们要去哪里？
Damn, this ain't a sight. Is where we're going like this?
- 更好 - 更好？
- Better. - Better?
树滴滴苹果像红色的宝石
Trees drippin' with apples like red jewels.
你认为你死了 发现了伊甸园
You think you'd died and found Eden.
- 你想要一个？ - 不 谢谢
- You want one? - No, thank you.
- 好吧
- All right.
什么让你想加入一束激进？
What made you want to join a bunch of radicals?
你知道世界的工业工人
Did you know the Industrial Workers of the World
是暴力无政府主义者还是肮脏的共产党人？
are violent anarchists and dirty Communists?
根据大多数民间
According to most folk.
- 和我的老人有很多关系
- Had a lot to do with my old man.
我看见那个可怜的老混蛋Joy让我想起了我的老人
Seein' that poor old bastard Joy reminded me of my old man.
他吃了这么多的殴打 他喝醉了
He took so many beatings that he went punch drunk.
有一次 我发现他走在街道中间的圆圈
One time, I found him walking in circles in the middle of the street.
有一双铜指节由一个疤痕真正的好
Got hit with a pair of brass knuckles by a scab real good.
之后不能直接转向
Never could steer straight after that.
- 他现在在哪里？
- Where's he at now?
- 他走了
- He's gone.
最后从警察的暴动枪上扣了胸部
Finally took charge a buckshot to the chest from a cop's riot gun.
说他死了 他甚至打地面
Say he was dead before he even hit the ground.
- 该死的 - 是的
- Damn. - Yeah.
你知道 我有这一切在我里面我从来没有任何地方放它
You know, I had all this inside me. I never had anywhere to put it.
我只是打了但现在我有机会争取的东西
I just fought. But now I have a chance to fight for something.
我想要争取的东西
I want to fight for something.
我要那个
I want that.
这就是我想要的
That's all I want.
- 我喜欢你的想法 吉姆•诺兰
- I like the way you think, Jim Nolan.
你和我会做一个很好的团队
You and me's gonna make a pretty good team.
你以前做过这样的事吗？不 永远
You ever do anything like this before? Nope, never.
关键是“他们不得不认为我们就像任何其他选择者
Gum. The key is' they gotta think we're like any other pickers,
让我们上班吧
Let's get to work.
你从哪里来的？向北 先生
Where you boys from? Up north, sir.
- 你两个选择之前？ - 是的先生
- You two pick before? - Yes, sir.
好吧 你为什么不找到一棵空树 去上班？
Well, why don't you find an empty tree and get to work?
- 好吧
- All right.
好吧 我得到了一个名字:伦敦
All right, I got a name: London.
找一棵树 挑 谈话给一些人 感觉到了
Find a tree, pick, talk to some folks, feel 'em out.
见ya后
See ya after.
- 不要伤害
- Don't bruise 'em.
腐烂在瘀伤 桶出来
Rot sets in a bruise, that bucket's out.
你听到了吗？ - 是啊 听
You hear me? - Yeah, hear.
- 你有问题 孩子？
- You got a problem, kid?
- 不 先生
- No, sir.
- 好吧 上帝 他很可怕 是吗？
- Well, God, he's awful, huh?
是啊这不是他 但
Yeah. It's not him, though.
这是整个设置是烂的我们要做什么？
It's this whole setup that's rotten. What are we gonna do about it'?
我不知道 但有些事情要做
I don't know, but somethings gotta be done.
- 是的
- Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
新人 跟我来我会告诉你你的床铺
New guys, follow me. I'll show you your bunks.
我以前看过他的类型
I seen his type before.
10到一个他是一个训练营士兵
10 to one he's a training camp soldier.
花了他的时间在战争冲击刺刀插入一袋锯木屑
Spent his time in the war punching a bayonet into a sack of sawdust
所以他回家没有看到一个沟
so he comes home without ever seeing a trench.
现在他是博尔顿的工头他的缺点
Now he's Bolton's foreman. His lackey.
他总是试图证明他是多么的艰难
He's always trying to prove how tough he is.
提醒我一个我以前知道的人在一天
Reminds me of a guy I used to know back in the day.
他的岩石离开了kick的狗
Got his rocks off kickin' dogs.
- 没有时间在这里观光
- No time for sightseeing here.
感觉到这里只是一点点在这里
Feel it down here. Just a little bit right here.
- 我不...在这里 - 让我们来看看
- I don't... right here. - Let's see.
哦 是的没关系
Ooh, yeah. It's okay.
嘿这是女性的铺位男人在这里
Hey. That's the women's bunks. Men's are over here.
- 好啦好啦
- Come on, come on.
床单在公司商店提供
Sheets are available in the company store.
你两个原因在这里麻烦 你走了
You two cause trouble here, you're gone.
- 哇
- Whew.
嘿 小心了 老定时器
Hey, careful up there, old timer.
小心？年轻的拳击手喜欢你
Careful? Young punks like you
有心脏衰竭看我的工作
have heart failure watching me work.
是这样吗？
Is that so?
一美元一天？相当陡峭的裁减
A dollar a day? Pretty steep cut.
你觉得怎么样？
What do you think about that?
我该怎么想？
What do I think about it?
我认为呜呜不会没有好
I think whining ain't gonna do no good.
是啊
Yeah.
- 最近怎么样'？
- How ya doin'?
我们必须漫游全国各地 像猪找工作
We gotta roam all over the country like hogs looking for work.
我们得到我们的屁股被剪贴板的家伙
And we get our ass beat by guys with clipboards.
如果我们坚持在一起 我们可以做一些改变
If we stuck together, we could really make some change.
- 嘿 听起来像希望
- Hey, that sounds like hope.
只有年轻人有好的希望
Only young'uns are good for hope.
我放弃了你可以拥有它
I gave it up. You can have it.
从来没有做我没有好
Never done me no good.
如果我们能做些什么呢？
What if there was something we could do about it?
看 我们听到你在说什么我们对你的政治不感兴趣
Look, we hear what you're saying. We ain't interested in your politics.
- 那就对了
- That's right.
政治 是吗？我只是想做什么是正确的
Politics, huh? I just want to do what's right.
- 好吧 看看
- Well, look.
支付我们少 比什么都不支付
Paying us less is better than paying nothing at all.
好吧 他们打了我们
Well, they gouge us
因为他们知道他们可以逃脱它
'cause they know they can get away with it.
- 我们已经说我们没有这个...
- We already said we ain't having this...
- 听 先生 一切应有的尊重
- Listen, Mister, with all due respect,
我不认识你
I don't know you.
我没有和你谈话
And I'm not having this conversation with you.
- 先生
- Sir.
可怜的混蛋
Poor bastards.
已经花钱 他们没有赚到只是为了吃饭
Already spending money they haven't earned just to get a meal.
没有什么比得到你的第一个薪水 已经欠了男人的钱
Nothing worse than getting your first paycheck and already owing the man money.
是的 没有一个厄运和阴暗 吉米
Yeah, none of that doom and gloom, Jimmy.
这里有很多喜欢
There's a lot to like here.
你可以感觉到紧张
You can feel the tension.
这就像水simmerin在它沸腾之前
It's like water simmerin' right before it boils over.
我今天设法与伦敦
I managed to get with London today.
他不会错过很多
He don't miss much.
但是他肯定会伤透薪酬
But he's sure sore as hell over the pay cut.
他是我们的家伙
He's our guy.
我们让他在我们身边
We get him over on our side,
他会和他一起摆动一堆僵尸
he'll swing a bunch of the stiffs with him.
他们会听他的
They'll listen to him.
- 有人生病了吗？
- Somebody sick?
伦敦的女她有一个婴儿
London's daughter-in-law. She's having a baby.
- 有医生？
- There a doctor?
不是没有人在这里打电话
Ain't nobody makes house calls out here.
- 来吧
- Come on.
- 是啊 你是开放的真正的好
- Yeah, you're openin' up real good.
你像一片叶子
You're shakin' like a leaf.
你确定你知道你在做什么吗？
You sure you know what the hell you're doing?
- 是啊真好真好
- Yeah, yeah. Real good. Real good.
你认为你在这里干什么？
What the hell you think you're doing here?
我们听说有一个女孩有一个婴儿
We heard there was a girl having a baby.
什么 你认为你只是进来 有一个甘德？
What, did you think you'd just come in and have a gander?
我们认为我们可能会帮助 看到你没有在这里的医生
We thought we might help, seeing as you don't have a doctor here.
- 好吧 你以前去过这儿吗？
- Well, you been around this before?
是的先生
Yes, sir.
- 哦 感谢上帝
- Oh, thank God.
所以 维拉在这里 她以前送牛犊
So, Vera here, she's delivered calves before,
但她不是没有...没有医生
but she ain't no... no doctor,
和这个老包在这里 我不知道她知道她在做什么
and this old bag here, I'm not sure she knows what she's doing either.
- 好 你在做...  - 夫人 你可以一边走
- Good, you're doing... - Ma'am, you can step aside.
嗯 这是真的你 先生 但我可以做到这一点
Well, that's real kind of you, sir, but I can do this.
- 你喝酒了吗？ - 不 我没有喝酒
- You been drinking? - No, I haven't been drinking.
我...我只是...我的手摇 这就是全部 - 你有没有打扰洗手？
I... I just... my hands shake, that's all. - Did you even bother to wash your hands?
就在旁边 那里让男人在这里工作
Just step aside, there. Let the man go to work here.
丽莎 它会好起来的这将是好的
Lisa, it's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
好吧？
All right?
嘿 丽莎 他...他们...这些家伙知道他们在做什么
Hey, Lisa, he... he... these guys know what they're doing.
他们已经在前面他们以前做过
They've been around it before. They've done this before.
这将是好的没关系
It's going to be okay. It's okay.
我们做了这100次 吉姆和我
We've done this 100 times, Jim and I.
我只需要一点点帮助父亲在哪里？
I just need a little more help. Where's the father?
他有一个意外三个月前过去了
He had an accident. Passed away three months ago.
- 我懂了好的
- I see. Okay.
好吧 把它放在我的肩上
All right, put that on my shoulders.
可以这样哭吗？这是好吗？
It's okay she's crying like this? This is okay?
- 嗯 是的 - 她没事
- Uh, yeah. - She's okay.
小心 - 好的
Look out. - Okay.
丽莎？丽莎？
Lisa? Lisa?
我是Mac这是吉姆现在 丽莎 当你感觉到它...
I'm Mac. This is Jim. Now, Lisa, when you feel it...
当你感到收缩时 我需要你推 好吗？
When you feel a contraction, I need you to push, okay?
帮助她 吉姆好吧
Help her out, Jim. All right.
帮助她 吉姆丽莎 你会好的 好吧？
Help her out, Jim. Lisa, you're gonna be just fine, all right?
你会很好只是看看我我们会一起做
You're gonna be just fine. Just look at me. We'll do it together.
当你感觉到收缩时 我需要你推
When you feel the contraction, I need you to push.
好的'？感觉吗？
Okay'? Feel it?
- 是的！ - 然后推！
- Yeah! - Then push!
推！你去吧！
And push! There you go!
你去了就是这样 就是这样
There you go. That's it, that's it.
来吧！来吧！来吧！
Come on! Come on! Come on!
现在推硬这是你的宝贝！
Push hard now. That's your baby!
来吧 丽莎就是这个 - 多一个多一个
Come on, Lisa. This is it. - One more. One more.
- 多一个 - 多一个
- One more. - One more.
推！
Push!
- 看那个女孩！啊 那是！
- Look at that, girl! Ah, there it is!
- 我们去！他在那！
- There we go! There he is!
他在那
There he is.
哦 不是很好吗？ - 抓住他抓住他
Oh, ain't that nice? - Hold him. Hold him.
你去了
There you go.
你做得很好 女孩你真的做到了
You did a good job, girl. You really did.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, mister.
你做了一件地狱谢谢 - 别客气
You did a hell of a thing. Thank you. - You're welcome.
- 你也是
- You, too.
非常感谢你 - 哦谢谢
Thank you very much. - Oh, thank you.
- 干得好 吉姆
- Good job, Jim.
是个男孩！
It's a boy!
嘿 Mac 来这里
Hey, Mac, come here.
- 什么？
- What?
什么？ - 你以前做过吗？
What? - You ever done that before?
- 交付宝宝？
- Delivered a baby?
我在军队有一些医疗训练
I had some medical training in the army.
我只是想我们会得到它尽可能干净
I just figured we'd get it as clean as possible
然后让自然接管
and then let nature take over.
我想这是一件好事 来了
I guess it's a good thing that came through,
或者我们会有很多麻烦
or we'd be in a lot of trouble.
- 你是一个ch子的疯狂的儿子
- You are a crazy son of a bitch.
你是一个子的一个疯狂的儿子
You're one crazy son of a bitch.
- 我被打得更糟了
- I've been called worse.
- 哦
- Ooh.
今晚有一个好东西 Mac
Did a good thing tonight, Mac.
真正的好东西
Real good thing.
- 当然 我猜是这样
- Sure, I guess so.
但重要的是我们让那些家伙在一起工作
But what matters is we got those guys working together.
我们有一个与伦敦
And we've got an in with London.
- 我们今晚送了一个婴儿 Mac
- We delivered a baby tonight, Mac.
这是值得的东西
That's gotta be worth something.
吉姆 听着 你得抓住每一个机会
Jim, listen, you gotta take every opportunity that you get.
我们必须记住什么是赌注
And we gotta remember what the stakes are.
我们正在努力改变数百万人的生活
We're trying to change things for millions of people.
任何人谁必须采取狗屎交易 因为老板说这样
Anyone who has to take a shit deal 'cause the boss says so.
任何人因为他们不拥有东西而受益
Anyone who gets taken advantage of 'cause they don't own something.
这是我们正在争取的对象
That's who we're fighting for.
这不是关于丽莎 它不是关于你和我
It's not about Lisa, it's not about you and me.
如果有什么 这是关于丽莎的孩子
If anything, it's about Lisa's kid,
和他会成长在什么样的世界
and what kinda world he's gonna grow up in.
如果我们想着自己或追逐荣耀
And if we're thinking about ourselves or chasing glory,
那么我们不会做到这一点
then we're not doing it right.
- 好吧 我明白了
- All right, I get it.
宝贝出来了 我差点出去了
Baby came out, I almost passed out.
我真的几乎失去了
I genuinely almost passed out.
嘿 我也是
Hey, me, too.
- 嘿 Mac
- Hey, Mac.
嘿 有 Mac
Hey, there, Mac.
- 你好朋友 - 最近怎么样'？
- Hey, buddy. - How ya doin'?
- 他们说话在这里？
- They talkin' strike out here yet?
嗯 是的他们很谨慎 但他们在谈论它
Mm, yeah. They're cautious, but they're talking about it.
- 嗯 这是一个开始
- Well, that's a start.
有些人甚至不会说
Some of these guys won't even say it.
喜欢 “罢工”是一个很好的字
Like, "strike“ is some kind cuss word,
和他们的母亲会用肥皂洗他们的嘴
and their mother'll come wash their mouths out with soap.
对于这样的人 你永远不知道什么会设置'
With people like this, you never know what'll set 'em off,
什么会得到巨石滚动
what'll get the boulder rolling.
看看'em
Just look at 'em.
他们需要一点推
All they needs a little push.
他们只是坐在路边
They were just sitting on the side of the road
旁边一个大白宫 我记得
next to a big white house, I remember.
嘿! - 不 我不是嘿!
Hey! - No, I'm not. Hey!
嘿 男孩 这是Mac 这里是吉姆
Hey, boys, this is Mac, and this here is Jim.
这些都是我告诉你的
These are the fellas I told you about.
那么 这些是照顾你的丽莎的口袋？
So, these are the fellas that took care of your Lisa?
- 那就对了
- That's right.
任何人都会这样做它不是
Any of you would have done the same. It was nothin'.
也许 但不是很多人的帮助一个陌生人
Maybe, but not many people'd help a stranger.
- 那么 伦敦？ - 嗯？
- So, London? - Hmm?
再想想我们昨天在说什么？
Think any more on what we were saying yesterday?
- 我想你说的话有意义
- I think what you said makes sense.
但是做麻烦从来没有让我任何地方
But making trouble never got me anywhere.
- 好吧 如果你不麻烦
- Well, if you don't make trouble,
然后nothings gonna变化
then nothings gonna change.
- 是的
- Yeah.
容易为你说我有一个家庭饲料
Easy for you to say. I got a family to feed.
是的 一个哥们回东东得到他的头骨破裂
Yeah, a buddy back East got his skull cracked
当他们试图组织
when they tried to organize.
好吧！得到他们的苹果
All right! Get to pickin' them apples.
好吧 让我们走吧
All right, let's go.
时间去挑他们苹果
Time to go pick them apples.
让我们继续前进 - 我们开始做吧
Let's move. - Let's do it.
来吧！
Come on!
- 伦敦？ - 是的
- London? - Yep.
一旦苹果被挑选 你去哪里？
Where you going once the apples get picked?
东 棉田
East, cotton fields.
好吧 你知道 确定如果他们在这里你
Well, you know for damn sure that if they cut you here,
他们会在棉花田里进一步削减
they're gonna cut even deeper in the cotton field.
嗯
Mm.
也许他是对的 - 是的 你知道他是对的
Maybe he's right. - Yeah, you know he's right.
吉姆这里是农业经济学的专家
Jim here is an expert on agricultural economics.
诚实对上帝 他比任何我知道更知道
Honest to God, he knows more than anyone I know
关于农场业务的方式
about the way the farm business goes.
-  Mm
- Mm.
我只是认为我们需要多谈一点
I just think that we need to talk about this a little bit more.
- 好吧
- All right.
伦敦 他们会削减和削减 直到我们做一些事情
London, they are gonna cut and cut until we do something about it.
-  Mm
- Mm.
- 嘿 Mac
- Hey, Mac.
我不知道农业经济学
I ain't knowin' nothin' about agriculture economics.
- 我以为你做了
- I thought you did.
-  Mornin' Dan - 嘿 你怎么会 孩子？
- Mornin', Dan. - Hey, how you doin', kid?
- 我做得很好你好吗'？ - 好
- I'm doin' all right. How you doin'? - Good.
你今天早点到了吗？
Did you get here early today?
是的 我这里真的很早
Yeah, I got here real early.
- 是的 对你有好处是啊
- Yeah, good for you. Yeah.
- 妈的 - 嘿 丹 是什么 你的腿？
- Oh, shit. - Hey, Dan, what is it, your leg?
- 你的腿断了吗？
- Is your leg broke?
王八蛋哪条腿是它？
Son of a bitch. Which leg is it'?
- 该死的！ - 它是什么腿？
- Damn! - What leg is it?
- 破坏的梯子 看！耶稣基督！
- Busted ladder, look! Jesus Christ!
移动 走出路 移动
Move, out of the way, move.
移动！
Move!
废话！ - 帮助我！
Bullshit! - Help me up!
- 有没有没有看到这里
- There ain't nothin' to see here.
这是一个坏了的梯子这是他的所有罪恶的错
It was a broken ladder. It's all his goddamn fault.
- 你听 男孩
- You listen, boy.
- 不 你听
- No, you listen.
- 抓住他！抓住他！
- Get him! Get him!
- 来吧！
- Come on!
嘿 打破它！
Hey, break it up!
嘿 下车他！你要杀他 因为基督的缘故
Hey, get off him! You're gonna kill him, for Christ's sake.
你要杀他 好吗？
You're gonna kill him, all right?
ya是什么？你在他们身边 还是什么？
What's it to ya? You on their side, or something?
不 我不在他们身边 上帝死了
No, I'm not on their side, God damn it.
好吧'！这不会帮助
All right'! This isn't gonna help.
- 让路！让路 备份
- Make way! Make way, back up.
来吧 弗兰克起床
Come on, Frank. Get up.
起来 男孩 - 你完成了
Get up, boy. - You're done.
- 不是现在不是现在
- Not now. Not now.
回去工作！ Y'all回工作！
Back to work! Y'all back to work!
告诉你一件事是肯定的 我不是工作在这些混蛋
Tell you one thing's for sure, I ain't workin' for these bastards.
不多一秒！ - 你死我们不是
Not one more second! - You goddamn right we're not.
伦敦 伦敦
London, London.
现在开始了
It's startin' now.
你在我父亲的头上是什么样的废话？
Just what sort of nonsense have you been puttin' in my father's head?
他不需要你的麻烦
He don't need your trouble.
- 妈妈 我明白你的忧虑
- Ma'am, I understand your concern.
不要你“妈妈”我来 爸爸 问他
Don't you “ma'am" me. Come on, Dad, ask him.
- 现在还是永远 - 伦敦！
- It is now or never. - London!
我们都遇到了为别人做好事的人
We've all met guys that have done good deeds for other people.
我们从来没有遇到过一个不想回报的人
We never met someone that didn't want something in return.
我们只是...只需要知道你的角度是什么
We just... just need to know what your angle is.
- 我的老人在这些领域工作
- My old man worked these fields.
多年前
Years ago.
他去那个城市 他不能再被围绕着
He went to the city when he couldn't take being jerked around any more.
他工作的工厂 直到他们开枪的那一天
He worked the factories up until the day they shot him
在胸部有一个荷载的负担
with a load of buckshot right in the chest.
你想知道他们为什么杀了他吗？
You wanna know why they killed him?
因为他有神经站起来说
Because he had the nerve to stand up and say
他们没有对待他
they weren't treating him right.
为此 他们像狗一样射杀他
And for that, they shot him like a dog.
这就是为什么总是像你和我的家伙
And that's how it's always been for guys like you and me.
那么 我们是谁？
So, who are we?
我们是要改变一切的人
We're the guys who are gonna change all that.
如果我们必须这样做 我们一定要做一个goddamn苹果字段
And we're gonna do it one goddamn apple field at a time if we have to.
好吧 现在如果我们要这样做 我们会这样做
All right, now if we're gonna do this, we're gonna do this right,
这意味着我们得快速组织
which means we gotta get organized quick
之前博尔顿可以在痂中运行
before Bolton can run in scabs.
但我们仍然需要有人来运行这个东西
But we still need somebody to run this thing.
那么 谁想提名某人？
So, who wants to nominate somebody?
- 我提名伦敦 - 好的
- I nominate London. - Okay.
任何人第二？
Anyone second that?
是啊！
Yeah!
好的 我们有其他提名吗？
All right, do we have any other nominations?
没有
No
好吧 我想我们有我们的领导
All right, I guess we have our leader.
好吧 那么 我想我也在想同样的事情
Okay, then, I guess I'm thinking the same thing
你们都思想' 大概
you all are thinkin', probably.
所以 我们现在住在这里如果这件事发生了 我们要去哪里？
So, we live here now. If this thing happens, where are we gonna go?
你说得对我们？！在！需要一个住宿地点
You're right. We?! at! need a place to stay.
你留给我们
You leave that to us.
- 到底是什么？
- What the hell was that about?
- 对不起 我使用了你老人的故事
- Sorry, I used your old man's story.
这是一个好故事
It's a good story.
我认为这是伦敦和所有他们...
I think it's what London and all them...
他们不得不在那时听到
They had to hear at that point.
如果你没有钱 你可以在房子里喝一杯咖啡
If you got no money, you can have a cup of coffee on the house,
但不要去秩序的食物 你不能支付
but don't go orderin' food you can't pay for,
认为你可以用完帐单
thinking you can run out on the bill.
你会是本周的第三选择者尝试
You'd be the third pickers this week to try that.
我们从这个城市送到这里去
We were sent here from the city on business.
我们听说你过去对我们的人有好处
We heard you been good to our people in the past,
我们不会忘记这样的事情
and we don't forget things like that.
我知道你you了看看ya
I knew you fellas had a look about ya.
我敢打赌你一整天都不吃我可以把东西放在ya吗？
I bet you haven't eaten all day. Can I put something on for ya?
- 听起来不错
- That sounds... - Great.
- 是的
- Yeah. - Okay.
我会回来的
I'll be right back.
所以 我听到你的流行音乐有一个自己的农场
So, I hear your pops has a farm of his own.
是的 我的老人有一些土地和一点果园
Yeah, my old man's got some land and a bit of an orchard.
嗯 我们想和他谈谈
Well, we'd like to talk to him.
我可以带你去那儿 但我得警告你
I can take you over there, but I gotta warn ya,
他是一个艰难的老git
he is a tough old git.
他不同情的原因
He's got no sympathy for causes.
嘿   这些fell想和你说话
Hey, pops, these fellas want to talk to you.
没有看到像这样的指针在很长时间
Ain't seen pointers like that in a long time.
可能你没有看到像这样的指针
Likely you ain't seen pointers like this ever.
- 是的你是鸟吗？ - 每个季节
- Yeah. You bird 'em? - Every season.
很多傻瓜使用安装工塞特的网狗
Yeah. Lot of fools use a setter. Setter's a net dog.
画家的枪狗
Painter's a gun dog.
- 是对的吗？
- Is that right?
你知道狗吗？ - 我做
You know dogs? - I do.
我喜欢这一个我喜欢她的样子
I like this one. I like the look of her.
- 是的 那是玛丽
- Yeah, that's Mary.
她在地里皮革的地狱弯曲
She's hell-bent for leather in the field.
从来没有见过一个狗盖地面像她
Never seen a dog cover ground like her.
我相信这个我叫McLeod
I believe it. My name's McLeod.
- 安德森
- Anderson.
麦克劳德你卖东西？
McLeod. You selling something?
- 不卖任何东西
- Not selling anything.
- 现在我能为你做什么 麦克劳德？
- Now what can I do for you, McLeod?
- 我要直接为你布局
- I'm going to lay it out for you straight.
几百个苹果选手将在明天这个时候罢工
A couple of hundred apple pickers will be on strike by this time tomorrow.
一旦他们打
As soon as they strike,
业主会离开他们的土地侵入
the owners are gonna kick 'em off their land for trespassing.
- 好吧 对于一个男人来说
- Well, for a man tellin' it straight,
你肯定需要很长时间才能得到点
you sure take a long time to get to the point.
好的-
. Okay-
这里说 你有五英亩的耕地
Al here says you have five acres of plowin' land.
这是私人财产 你可以做你可以
That's private property that you can do with as you please.
让我们在你的土地上营地
Let us make camp on your land.
我们会免费挑选你的苹果
We'll pick your apples for free.
你将是市场上整个县唯一的作物
Yours'll be the only crop in the entire county at market-.
你会杀了
You'll make a killing.
我得和我的邻居相处他们会给我地狱 我做了这样的事情
I gotta get along with my neighbors. They'd give me hell, I did a thing like that.
- 你拥有这片土地吗？ - 我做
- You own this land? - I do.
- 清楚吗？
- Is it clear?
好吧 地狱 不 它不清楚我有一个抵押贷款
Well, hell, no, it's not clear. I got a mortgage.
- 和谁？
- With whom?
-  Torgas金融
- Torgas Finance.
- 谁拥有Torgas金融？
- And who owns Torgas Finance?
我会告诉你...马丁 猎人 博尔顿
I'll tell you... Martin, Hunter, Bolton.
这三个混蛋拥有这个山谷90％的耕地
Same three bastards own 90% of the farming land in this valley.
他们被挤压了？
They been squeezin' ya?
他们把你挤出来多久了？
How long till they squeeze you out?
一年？
A Year?
现在 假设你在一个不断上涨的市场上卖你的整个作物
Now, suppose you sell your whole crop in a rising market.
你支付的庄稼没有采摘
A crop you paid nothing to have picked,
它可能让你失去这个按揭
It might get you out of that mortgage.
然后他们不能碰你
And then they couldn't touch you.
嗯 我不知道我可以信任一对红军
Well, I'm not sure I can trust a couple of Reds.
你试过信任Torgas Finance那怎么办？
You tried trusting Torgas Finance. How'd that work out for ya'?
这样考虑
Consider it this way.
当你还有机会把它粘在克里斯•博尔顿吗？
When else are you gonna get a chance to stick it to Chris Bolton?
- 我喜欢他
- I like him.
他是一个脾气暴躁的老混蛋 但我喜欢他
He's a grumpy old bastard, but I like him.
- 你不喜欢人 吉姆
- Don't you go liking people, Jim.
我们不能浪费时间喜欢人
We can't afford to waste time liking people.
我知道你认为这是冷的 但我只是实际
I know you think that's cold, but I'm just being practical.
- 好吧 我明白了
- All right, I get it.
所以 实际上 你怎么总是知道怎么说对这样的家伙？
So, speaking practically, how do you always know what to say to guys like that'?
这不难你只是告诉他们他们想听什么
It's not hard. You just tell 'em what they want to hear.
当然 但你怎么知道他们想听什么？
Sure, but how do you know what they wanna hear?
- 好...
- Well...
看 那样的人...
See, guys like that...
他们认为他们想要财富或权力或安全
they think they want wealth or power or security.
没有什么重要
None of that matters.
他们只是想感觉他们的生活很重要
They just want to feel like their lives matter.
喜欢他们重要
Like they matter.
他们想认为他们对自己的生活有一定的控制
They want to think that they have some control over their lives.
- 而已？
- That's it?
丽莎 我只是说 我们不能相信这些家伙
Lisa, I'm just saying, we can't trust these guys.
我们不知道他们是谁 好吗？你必须要小心
We don't know who they are, okay? You have to be careful.
Vinnie 我想喂婴儿你能离开吗？
Vinnie, I'm trying to feed the baby. Can you please leave?
- 嗨
- Hi.
嘿 我不是想打扰你我知道 嗯...
Hey, I don't mean to bother you. I know, um...
我给你带了一些汤
I brought you some soup.
这是你的甜蜜你可以把它放在这里
That's sweet of you. You can put it here.
- 我要把它放在这里
- I'm gonna put it here.
- 你为什么不坐下来？
- Why don't you sit down?
你要我坐吗？好 当然
You want me to sit? Yeah, sure.
所以...哦 对不起 - 你不必这样做
So... oh, sorry about that. - You don't have to do that.
想象你已经看到了超过这个反正
Figured you've already seen more than this anyway.
- 你感觉怎么样？
- How are you feeling?
- 累了
- Rm tired.
考虑到我推这个一个离开我
Considering I pushed this one outta me.
- 这就说得通了
- That makes sense.
他怎么样？
How's he doin'?
- 你想拿他吗？
- You wanna hold him?
- 做...我想抱着宝宝吗？
- Do... do I want to hold the baby?
- 在这里 试试 - 哦那好吧
- Here, try. - Oh, all right.
- 由头 - 好的
- By the head. - Okay.
只是 呃...
Just, uh...
天啊
Oh, man.
- 我叫他约西亚
- I named him Josiah.
- 嗨 Josiah
- Hi, Josiah.
他很漂亮
He's beautiful.
我对父亲很抱歉
I'm sorry about the father.
- 没有意外
- There was no accident.
当他发现我怀孕时 懦夫跑了
The coward ran off when he found out I was pregnant.
上帝 我甚至不知道为什么我告诉你
God, I don't even know why I told you.
不要告诉任何人 - 我不会告诉任何人
Don't tell anyone. - I won't tell anyone.
- 伦敦比我更more
- London's more ashamed than I am.
- 好吧 我不会告诉任何人
- Well, I won't tell anyone.
- 你是个好人 不是吗 吉姆？
- You're a good man, aren't you, Jim?
- 我试图成为
- I try to be.
Mach:Bolton知道我们走开了工作
Mach: Bolton knows we walked off the job.
而且Edie说他今天带来的疤痕取代了我们
And Edie says he's bringing in scabs today to replace us.
所以 我们必须说服疤痕加入我们
So, we gotta convince the scabs to join us
或警示会在它开始之前结束
or the strike will be over before it even begins.
挂断 - 你知道我不知道的东西吗？
Hang back. - Do you know something I don't?
这些警察要看看谁是领导是
These cops are gonna be lookin' to see who the leader is.
我不想对任何人注意自己
I don't want to call any attention to ourselves.
- 不介意他们
- Never mind them.
我们都在这一边
We're all on the same side here.
我们的战斗不是与你
Our fight is not with you.
你必须加入我们
You gotta join us,
和我们一起 我们会得到他们欠我们的钱
and together we'll get 'em to pay what they owe us.
- 是啊！
- Yeah, yeah!
这个人的权利 由神！
This man's right, by God!
我们为什么要为一个认为自己拥有我们的人工作？
Why should we work for a man who think they own us?
- 来吧 - 抱紧
- Come on. - Hold back.
- 我们得停下来 - 你知道他们对你的想法吗？
- We gotta stop 'em. - You know what they think of you?
他们认为你是泥土
They think you're dirt.
他们认为你是垃圾
They think you're trash.
他们认为他们可以只是咀嚼你 吐出你
They think they can just chew you up, spit you out,
从你做的工作中获取利润
take the profits from the work that you do
与你的汗水和你的血
with your sweat and your blood.
而这些警察 这些猪
And these cops, these pigs,
你知道他们做什么 当你尝试
you know what they do when you try
行使你作为免费美国人的权利？
to exercise your rights as a free American?
他们在骷髅打你 他们敲出你的牙齿
They bash you in the skull, they knock out your teeth,
他们踢在肋骨
they kick in the ribs,
打电话给你一块狗屎
call you a piece of shit.
现在我们应该为他们工作？
And now we're supposed to work for them?
他们是母狗的儿子 我告诉你
They're sons of bitches, I tell you.
你知道我们是从哪里来的？
And you know what we do with sons of bitches where I come from?
喜悦！
Joy!
- 喜悦！
- Joy!
- 天啊
- Oh, God.
- 回来！
- Get back!
- 他死了
- He's dead.
他死了他死了！
He's dead. He's dead!
- 你们全部去死吧！
- You can all go to hell!
你所有的人
All you folks,
你选了我当这个组的主席
you elected me to be chairman of this here group.
我想这意味着我应该 ...
I guess that means I'm supposed to...
在这里代表这个可怜的人说些什么
say something on behalf of this poor man here.
好 我不擅长演讲
Well, I'm not good at speeches.
但你看到了他发生了什么
But you saw what happened to him.
他没有试图伤害任何人
He wasn't trying to harm nobody.
他刚刚和我们站在一起
He just came to stand with us.
这里有一个男人 Mac 谁知道他
There's a man here, Mac, who knew him.
去那里 Mac
Go ahead up there, Mac.
-  Ahem是的 我认识他
- Ahem. Yeah, I knew him.
他是我的朋友
He was my friend.
他的名字是Joy
His name was Joy,
他是一个激进派
He was a radical.
你听到了我
You heard me.
他是一个真正的激进
He was a true radical.
他是一个激进的 因为他想要像你和我这样的人
He was a radical because he wanted people like you and me
有足够的吃饭和一个地方睡觉
to have enough to eat and a place to sleep.
他自己不想要什么
He didn't want nothing for himself.
他不想要一个邪恶的事情
He didn't want a goddamn thing.
他是一个激进派！
He was a radical!
一个肮脏的混蛋
A dirty bastard,
对政府的危险
a danger to the government
因为他想让我们所有人都有一个公平的镜头
because he wanted all of us to have a fair shot.
所以警察打他了
So the cops beat him to pieces.
他们打破了他的手这么多次 他不能做一个拳头
They broke his hands so many times he couldn't make a fist.
他们打破了他的下巴 所以他不能吃得对
They busted his jaw so he couldn't eat right.
现在他们在我们脚下射杀他
And now they shot him, right at our feet.
你要做什么呢？
What are you going to do about it?!
你要把他扔在泥坑里
You gonna dump him in a mud hole,
把一些雪泥抹在他身上 忘记了吗？没有！
put some slush over him and forget it? No!
他为你而战！你要忘记他吗？
He was fighting for you! Are you going to forget about him?
没有！ - 你会躺下 只是把它？
No! - Are you gonna lie down and just take it?
没有！
No!
你要让他们远离杀死他吗？
Are you going to let them get away with killing him?
没有！ - 他是我们中的一个
No! - He was one of us.
那么你要做什么呢？
So what are you gonna do about it?
斗争！
Fight!
什么？
What? Fight!
- 你要打？ - 那就对了
- You gonna fight? - That's right.
- 我们要为他而战
- We're going to fight for him.
我们要为我们战斗
And we're going to fight for us.
但我们不能用枪打他们
But we can't fight them with guns.
我们不能用刀子打他们
We can't fight them with knives.
那么我们要做什么？
So what are we gonna do?
- 打击！罢工！ - 那就对了！
- Strike! Strike! - That's right!
罢工！罢工！ - 打击！罢工！
Strike! Strike! - Strike! Strike!
罢工！
Strike!
我们将组织一个干净的营地
We'll run a clean camp, organized.
没有酒
No booze.
我们有一个名叫Edie的女人
We got a woman by the name of Edie,
谁通过卡车装载物资
who's bringing in supplies by the truckload.
我们有一个负责健康和卫生的文件
And we got a doc in charge of health and sanitation.
我的人民知道他们在做什么
My people know what they're doing,
我们将免费为您的整个果园挑选
and we'll have your entire orchard picked in no time, for free.
就这样
That does it.
- 好吧
- All right.
每天三块钱 我们不会走开！
Three bucks a day and we won't walk away!
这真的发生了看看'em
This is really happening. Look at 'em.
这就像他们从一个长睡眠醒来
It's like they're waking up from a long sleep.
- 我所看到的是危险
- All I see is danger.
哦 来吧不危险这是可能性 看看
Oh, come on. Not danger. This is possibility, look.
看看大家如果他们都像这样一起工作
Look at everyone. If they all keep working together like this,
没有什么我们不能做
there's nothing we can't do.
- 我知道这些人它不能持续
- I know these men. It can't last.
你应该对你的同胞有更多的信心
You should have more faith in your fellow man.
他们会发痒 他们会开始战斗
They'll get itchy, and they'll start fighting.
我们将帮助您保持正确的道路我们会变成形状
We'll help 'em stay on the right path. We'll whip 'em into shape.
- 真的吗？ - 是的是啊
- Oh, really? - Yeah. Yeah.
- 我希望你可以
- I hope you can.
我只是希望你知道你在做什么
I just hope you know what you're doing.
说 不是那个你有眼睛的女人？
Say, ain't that the lady you had your eye on'?
- 当然是
- Sure is.
那么 这是一个耻辱她的男人
Well, that's a shame about her man dyin'.
有人会帮助抚养那个宝宝
Someone's gonna have to help raise that baby.
说 你认为吉姆•诺兰的家伙 反正呢？
Say, what do you think of that Jim Nolan guy, anyway?
- 他不是不是特别
- He ain't nothin' special.
- 我想他没事
- I think he's all right.
嘿 等等
Hey, wait up.
- 苹果电脑'？ - 是的
- Mac'? - Yeah.
- 我要去看看文档
- I'm gonna head to see the doc.
- 你告诉我什么？
- What the hell are you telling me for?
你告诉我不要不要不让你知道 所以...
You told me not to do nothin' without letting you know, so...
- 耶稣基督
- Jesus Christ.
您一定会按照指示进行什么都别管 继续我会在那里有一点
You sure follow directions. Just go on. I'll be there in a bit.
- 是啊 我只是告诉你
- Yeah, I was just tellin' ya.
耶稣
Jesus.
不 先生 我不想要任何废话
No, sir, I don't want any of that nonsense,
但是 不 这...  -  Doc'？ Doc 对不起
but, no, this... - Doc'? Doc, sorry.
- 我能为你做什么 吉姆？
- What can I do for you, Jim?
好吧 我只想看看你是否需要任何帮助
Well, I just wanted to see if you needed any help
和 呃 艾迪说 她有 呃...
and, uh, Edie says that she has the, uh...
你叫什么？消毒剂
What do you call it? Disinfectant.
啊那个女人是美好的 神话般的 是的
Ah. That woman is wonderful, fabulous, yeah.
帮助 是的 总是
Help, yeah, always.
来
Come.
好吧 Mac和Edie肯定有了这个
Well, Mac and Edie certainly got this one
并快速运行
up and running pretty quickly.
幸运的他们那可怜的老sot
Lucky for them that poor old sot
采取了他做的时候他做的秋天
took the fall that he did when he did.
是的 男人们没有真正承诺 是吗？
Yeah, the men weren't really committed, were they?
直到老年喜悦举起他的最后一个立场
Not until old Joy put up his last stand.
- 你在说什么？
- What are you talking about?
- 没有
- Nothing.
只是对这个偶然的时机做一个评论
Just making a remark about this serendipitous timing.
Mac说 你不是致力于我们的事业 但你无论如何帮助我们
Mac says that you're not committed to our cause, but you help us anyway.
啊 你不想说我的政治理论 至少不是现在
Ah, you don't want to be talking about my political theories, at least not now.
你是新来的 是吗？
You're new to this, huh?
你对你的新同志有什么？
What do you make of your new comrades?
你觉得他们鼓舞人心吗？
Do you find them inspiring?
- 嗯 是的 我做 - 是啊？
- Uh, yeah, I do. - Yeah?
- 我做 诚实对上帝
- I do, honest to God.
我真的发现他们鼓舞人心
I really do find them inspiring.
- 好
- Good.
博尔顿在这里 博尔顿在这里
Bolton's here, Bolton's here.
- 伦敦 我想
- London, I presume.
我被告知你是负责这个 这个聚会的人
I've been told you're the man in charge of this, uh... this gathering.
那就对了
That's right.
- 我叫Bolton
- My name's Bolton.
是的 我知道你是谁 - 是...
Yeah, I know who you are. - Yeah...
我希望我们能谈论
I was hoping we could talk.
- 好吧
- All right.
- 好的？ - 当然
- Okay? - Sure.
你为什么不滑溜了一点
Why don't you skedaddle for a bit. Go ahead.
来吧 让我们走吧 让我们走吧
Come on, let's go, let's go.
- 哦
- Oh.
博尔顿先生 你为什么不坐在我的办公室？在这里
Mr. Bolton, why don't you just sit right in my office? Right here.
- 我是唯一一个坐 是吗？
- I'm the only one sitting, huh?
- 是的 - 老人
- Yeah. - The old man.
你真的认为你需要一个友好的谈话吗？
You really think you need that for a friendly talk'?
没关系 维拉让男人有他的枪
It's all right, Vera. Let the man have his gun.
- 现在 这是我的女儿 爱丽丝
- Now, this is my daughter, Alice.
作为我的事业的继承人 我认为这很重要
As the heir to my business, I think it is important
她亲眼看到男人和女人
that she sees firsthand the men and the women
谁会为她工作
who will be working for her.
他们不属于这里
They don't belong here.
摆脱他们我们不需要em
Get rid of them. We don't need 'em.
- 呃 你的男人留下来 我的男人留下来
- Uh, your men stay, my men stay.
好的-
. Okay-
你知道你在做什么吗？我知道这些争吵的人
You know what you're getting into? I know about these rabble-rousers.
他们不会给你一个伤害
They don't give a damn about you.
- 看 只是说你的一块 老板的人
- Look, just say your piece, boss man.
- 好吧 是的就这样吧
- Okay, so be it. So be it.
我们都是忙碌的人;我会得到的权利
We're both busy men; I'll get right to the point.
你带这些人回来工作
You bring these men back to work,
我会让你助理监督
I'll make you assistant superintendent.
一个稳定的工作
A steady job.
每天五美元
Five dollars a day.
- 真的吗？ - 是的
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
- 你会买我吗？ - 不不不
- You're gonna buy me off? - No, no, no.
- 一个机会舔你的靴子？
- A chance to lick your boots?
请
Please.
你很幸运我不冷鸡巴你的屁股在这里
You're lucky I don't cold-cock your ass right here.
-  Just easy别紧张
- Just easy. Take it easy.
好的
Okay.
现在 我发现在任何争端
Now, I find in any dispute,
如果双方坐在桌边 他们可以工作
if the two parties sit down at the table, they can work things out.
- 嗯 我们没有没有表
- Well, we ain't got no table.
好吧 这混乱不是好事的任何人 好吗？
Well, this mess isn't good business for anyone, all right'?
现在 回来工作
Now, come back to work.
你会得到你的工资 我们会得到我们的苹果
You'll get your wages, we'll get our apples picked.
好吧？每个人都会快乐 快乐快乐-
All right? Everybody will be happy, happy. happy-
没有影响 没有怨恨
No repercussions, no grudges.
- 什么...
- What...
有什么优惠？
What's the offer?
这是提议回来工作
That is the offer. Come back to work.
- 是的 但是以什么速度？ - 我们讨论的速率
- Yeah, but at what rate? - The rate we discussed.
一美元一天
A dollar a day.
- 耶稣 你密吗？
- Jesus, are you dense?
我是说 你是什么...
I mean, what do you...
你认为我们在这里惊人的是什么？
What do you think we're striking about here?
- 一美元二十
- A dollar twenty.
没有问题没有怨恨这就是我能去的高度
No questions no grudges. That's as high as I can go.
$ 1.20
$1.20.
- 鲍勃 把你的手下来
- Bob, put your damn hand down.
这不到你承诺的一半
That's less than half of what you promised.
想想女人想想他们 好吗？
Think of the womenfolk. Think of them, all right'?
这些小姐们在这里需要照顾像他们的皇后
These fine ladies here need to be taken care of like the queens they are.
- 博尔顿先生 我看到的方式
- Mr. Bolton, the way I see it
是我认为没有我们很清楚
is I think it's pretty clear without us,
你的苹果不被挑选
your apples don't get picked.
我们不会选择任何苹果 直到我们得到我们承诺的工资
And we're not picking any apples until we get the wages that we were promised.
- 把你的卡 Bolton
- Turn your cards over, Bolton.
我们看到你已经雇佣了这些Pinkerton杂种之一
We see you already hired one of these Pinkerton bastards.
那么 什么是“或者”？
So, what's the "or else"?
我们回来为你工作 否则你会放出警惕的？
We come back and work for you or else you're gonna let out the vigilantes?
-  Vigilantes？
- Vigilantes?
我可以向你保证 我不知道你在说什么
I can assure you I have no idea what you're talking about.
但如果愤怒的公民团结在一起
But if outraged citizens band together
保持和平
to keep the peace,
这是他们的上帝给予的权利
that's their God-given right.
如果你继续罢工
And if you keep on with the strike,
我们将被迫向总督请愿
we'll be forced to petition the governor for troops.
我们在这里的私人土地上你没有权利推我们离开
We're on private land here. You got no right to push us off.
哦耶？好吧 我们会看看
Oh, yeah? Well, we'll see about that.
我曾经希望你能听听理性我真的做到了
I had hoped you would listen to reason. I really did.
但你强迫我的手
But you're forcing my hand.
如果你继续这个愚蠢
And if you continue with this foolishness,
知道我会粉碎这次罢工
know that I will crush this strike
并埋葬你们每一个人
and bury each and every one of you.
这是一个承诺
That's a promise.
- 博尔顿 你粗暴地安德森
- Bolton, you rough up Anderson,
你触摸他的财产 你触摸一个goddamn苹果树
you touch his property, you touch one goddamn apple tree,
我们会烧毁每个房子和谷仓
we will bum down every house and barn
在这个山谷的每个牧场
on every ranch in this valley.
让路 人让路
Make way, people. Make way.
让路
Make way.
- 丽莎
- Lisa.
博尔顿现在将开始打击它会变得丑陋
Bolton will start cracking down now. It'll get ugly.
哦 来吧 Doc男人将能够处理它
Oh, come on, Doc. The men will be able to handle it.
他们知道这是多么重要他们会打架 他们不会打破
They know how important this is. They'll fight, they won't break.
我希望我能看到它与你的清晰 吉姆
I wish I could see it with your clarity, Jim.
男人 他遇到了 他击败了每一个障碍
Man, he's met and he's defeated every obstacle,
每个敌人 但只有一个
every enemy but... but one.
他只是不能反对自己
He just can't win against himself.
人类讨厌自己
Mankind hates itself.
我们不恨人类
We don't hate mankind.
我们讨厌压迫工人的制度
We hate the system that oppresses working people.
堆叠甲板的系统 所以一些人有一切
The system that stacks the deck so a few people have everything.
我们其余的人必须战胜废墟这就是我们讨厌的
The rest of us have to fight over the scraps. That's what we hate.
另一边由男人组成 吉姆 男人喜欢你
The other side is made up of men too, Jim, men like you.
你怎么看这一切？
What do you think about all this?
你对这种情况的评价是什么？
What's your assessment of this situation?
- 我想要的只是一个简单 干净的生活
- All I want is just a simple, clean life.
一个农场和一个房子 一个家庭
A farm and a house, a family-.
有人帮助提高约西亚
Somebody to help raise Josiah with.
所有的休息只是感觉像不必要的复杂性
All the rest just feels like needless complication.
丽莎 你不明白吗？这就是为什么我这样做
Lisa, don't you see? That's why I'm doing this.
我为你和像你这样的人这样做
I'm doing this for you and for people like you,
所以他们有一个镜头在那生活
so they have a shot at that life.
但是 Mac 告诉大家做什么
But that Mac, telling everyone what to do,
他只是看起来很冷
he just seems so cold.
- 不 Mac不冷
- No, Mac isn't cold.
所有这些微笑 它就像我们在拼图板上的棋子
All those smiles, it's like we're pieces on a puzzle board.
在那个应该温暖的地方刚刚走了
That place in him that's supposed to be warm is just gone.
如果这是所有这一切的成本 这是不对的 是吗？
If that's the cost of all this, it ain't right, is it?
“嘿 Doc？”嗯？
" Hey, Doc? " Hmm?
- 你认为我会是一个好父亲？
- You think I'd be a good father?
- 是的 我想你会是一个好父亲
- Yeah, I think you'd be a good father.
Hey-
. Hey-
- 耶稣基督 你在哪里？
- Jesus Christ, where you been?
供应是如此干燥 我是spittin'棉花
The supplies are so dry, I'm spittin' cotton.
- 看这个
- Look at this.
- 耶稣基督
- Jesus Christ.
- 它是什么？
- What is it?
- “县投票给肉食者
- "County Votes to Feed Strikers.
昨晚在公开会议上 监事会
At a public meeting last night, the Board of Supervisors
一致投票给现在打击苹果种植者的男人
unanimously voted to feed the men now striking against the apple growers."
- 嗯 如果他们想给我们食物...
- Well, if they want to give us food...
- 不 假人这是一个老伎俩
- No, dummy. It's an old trick.
我有同情者排队 准备好给我们
I have sympathizers lined up, ready to give us
食物和毯子和钱 然后这出来了
food and blankets and money, then this comes out
他们说 “为什么我喂你什么？
and they say, "Why am I feeding you anything?
县一直在喂你我在纸上看到了
County's been feeding you. I saw it in the paper."
但你准备好了事情会变坏
But you be ready. Things are gonna get bad.
博尔顿会开始打击
Bolton's gonna start cracking down
男人的决心将开始减弱
and the men's resolve will start to weaken.
- 你失去信心 爱迪？
- You losing faith, Edie?
我是一个现实主义者 总是一直 总是会
I'm a realist, always have been, always will be.
她是对的它会变得丑陋
She's right. It's gonna get ugly.
但这对我们有好处
But that's good for us.
越糟糕 故事越大
The worse it gets, the bigger the story,
对事业的更多同情
the more sympathy for the cause.
只需要确保罢工持续进行
Just have to make sure the strike keeps going.
你们只是看着
The guys'll stay strong. You just watch.
我承诺 - 来吧
I promise. - Come on.
- 嗯？我们在哪里？
- Huh? Where we goin'?
- 进入城市 - 马上？
- Gotta get into town. - Right now?
- 是的 - 哦 狗屎
- Yeah. - Oh, shit.
而已？只是发送一些信件？
That's it? Just send some letters?
那就对了
That's right. Now we gotta wait.
希望我的家伙有一些想法
Hopefully my guys'll have some ideas
如何推回对Bolton
on how to push back against Bolton.
晚饭
Evenin', fellas.
- 即使在'只是出来一点漫步
- Evenin'. Just out for a little stroll.
这是一条公路 好吗？我们被允许走在它上面
It's a public road, all right? We're allowed to walk on it.
- 然后走
- Then walk.
步行 - 你没有理由
Walk. - You got no cause.
你要我们跟你一起去 你得逮捕我们
You want us to go with you, you gotta arrest us.
然后你要跟我们的律师谈谈
Then you're gonna have to talk to our lawyers.
谁对警察说什么？我说走
Who said anything about police? I said walk.
- 好吧
- All right.
- 移动
- Move.
叫弗兰克 对吧？
Call you Frank, right?
是啊 你有话要说 伙计？
Yeah, you got something to say, buddy?
说吧张开嘴
Say it. Open your mouth.
- 是的
- Yeah.
像你这样的人是任何城镇中最脏的混蛋
Guys like you are the dirtiest bastards in any town.
你是那些喜欢在hobos和lynch黑人攻击的人
You're the ones who like to beat on hobos and lynch Negroes.
你可以打扮 称它保持和平
You can dress it up, call it keeping the peace,
但你只是想残忍
but you just like to be cruel.
喜欢打一个家伙 如果他被绑起来或超过10对一个
Like to beat on a guy if he's tied up or outnumbered 10 to one,
但你永远不会面对他人的男人
but you'd never face him man to man.
- 哦耶？
- Oh, yeah?
你的意思是这样吗？
You mean like this?
- 是的
- Yeah.
跑！
Run!
跑！跑！ - 射他！
Run! Run! - Shoot him!
射他！拍他 拍他 拍他！
Shoot him! Shoot him, shoot him, shoot him!
射他！
Shoot him!
上帝死了 拍他！
God damn it, shoot him!
他妈的！
God damn it!
让我们去吧我们只有时间
Let 'em go. We got nothing but time.
哦 你会再见到我们！
Oh, you're gonna be seeing us again!
我们知道你肮脏的朋友
And we know your dirty friends,
我们要付每一次的访问！
and we're gonna pay each of 'em a visit!
- 这是什么东西？
- What the hell was that?
这是我们正在处理的人的味道
That was a taste of who we're dealing with.
他们能做到吗？我们没有违反任何法律
Can they do that? We didn't break any laws.
他们可以做任何他们想要的
They can do whatever they want.
没有人停下来
No one stops 'em.
来吧！
Come on out!
- 他们会继续来在我们后面
- They're gonna keep coming after us.
来吧 让我们回到营地
Come on, let's get back to camp,
让我们知道他们在那里 好吗？
let 'em know that they're out there, all right?
上 上帝！
on, God!
好吧？是啊
All right? Yeah.
嘿 - 你的混蛋应该保护我们
Hey. - You bastards are supposed to protect us.
- 怎么了？
- What's the matter?
怎么了？一群人烧了
What's the matter? Bunch of men burned
Al的午餐货车清澈到地面
Al's Lunch Wagon clear to the ground.
这是什么事
That's what's the matter.
- 整个死神的事
- The whole goddamn thing.
嘿 Al
Hey, Al.
希望你快乐新
Hope you're happy new
看看到底是什么？
See what comes of it?
看看他躺在那里
Look at him laying there.
我们把1,800美元放进那个晚餐
We put $1,800 into that diner.
- 为了基督的缘故 爸爸 不要开始
- For Christ's sake, Dad, don't start.
- 嘿 我们觉得糟糕
- Hey, we feel awful bad.
好吧 让他休息一下 Mac
All right, let him get some rest, Mac.
- 好吧
- All right.
- 这是要伤害 Al
- This is gonna hurt, Al.
- 我们会把额外的卫兵...  - 出去
- We'll put extra guards... - Get out.
- 是的先生
- Yes, sir.
警卫在哪里？
Where are the guards?
他妈的 - 搞什么鬼？
God damn it. - What the hell?
- 放松 人是不是没人在身边
- Relax, man. Ain't nobody around.
这不是一个笑话 好吗？我们欠安德森先生
This isn't a joke, okay? We owe Mr. Anderson.
我们疲惫了我们整天纠察
We're exhausted. We been picketing all day.
- 耶稣 足够的借口
- Jesus, enough with the excuses.
你们两个不能做呢？找到可以的人！
You two can't do it? Find someone who can!
- 你不是我们的老板 - 不 我不是
- You ain't our boss. - No, I ain't.
但是你认为伦敦在发现时会做什么
But what do you think London's gonna do when he finds out
你两个不是pullin'你的体重？
you two ain't pullin' your weight?
- 伦敦不是我们的老板
- London ain't our boss neither.
你是对的但他可以用双手撕裂你的肢体
You're right. But he can tear you limb from limb with his bare hands.
现在 得到outta这里！我不想让你两个守卫谷仓
Now, get outta here! I don't want you two guarding the barn.
我们走吧！
Let's go!
如果我不觉得我们做到了穷人Al
Damn if I don't feel like we did that to poor Al.
我的意思是 午餐车 这是他的一生
I mean, that lunch wagon, that was his whole life.
不要去想这样你没有打破Al的肋骨
Don't go thinkin' that way. You didn't bust Al's ribs.
他们的博士工作
Them bastards work for Bolton did.
- 好吧 但我不能帮助...
- All right, but I can't help...
我不能帮助感觉像...
I can't help feelin' like...
我的意思是 你看到安德森先生的眼睛吗？
I mean, did you see the look in Mr. Anderson's eyes?
我不会对你说谎... Hatin是最难的部分
I ain't gonna lie to you... Hatin's the hardest part.
你做我们做的事 每个人都讨厌你
You do what we do, everyone hates you,
敌人 我们身边
the enemy, our side both.
这是他们的整个计划
That's their whole plan.
他们会把我们分开一点点 直到整个事情崩溃
They're gonna divide us a bit at a time until the whole thing falls apart.
但我们不会让我们
But we ain't gonna let 'em.
- 我不能停止思考喜悦 只是...
- I can't stop thinking about Joy, just...
射击到地狱
shot to hell.
- 我也是 吉姆
- Me too, Jim.
我也是
Me too.
这很值得
It's worth it.
吃点东西
Get something to eat.
哇！嘿！
Whoa, hey. Hey! Hey!
- 得到 Vinnie - 哇！
- Get 'em, Vinnie. - Whoa!
哇！
Whoo!
- 得到 吉姆 - 你在做什么？嘿 停下来！
- Get 'em, Jim. - What are you doing? Hey, stop it!
停止m停止！哎停止
Stop m Stop! Hey, stop
你在干什么？嘿嘿嘿hey-
What are you guys doing? Hey, hey, hey. hey-
嘿 我们只是做Mac告诉我们做的
Hey, we're just doing what Mac told us to do.
Mac告诉你这样做？
Mac told you to do this?
来吧 让我们走吧去去去去！
Come on, let's go. Go, go, go, go!
- 来吧 狗屎 - 跑！跑！
- Come on, shit. - Run! Run!
他们得到枪！ - 耶稣基督！
They got guns! - Jesus Christ!
- 嘿 奶子！
- Hey, fellas!
你不会来找你的同志吗？
Aren't you gonna come get your comrade?
什么 你现在支持？
What, you backin' out now?
- 我不知道 只是...
- I don't know, just...
我只是没有想到任何人会得到
I just didn't think anybody would get hun.
那么 你认为会发生什么
Well, what exactly did you think would happen
当你穿过像博尔顿这样的人吗？
when you cross a man like Bolton?
你认为他只是翻身 给我们想要什么？
You think he'd just roll over and give us what we wanted?
- 我认识比利他的一生
- I'd known Billy his whole life.
现在 这太多了
Now, this is just too much.
Mm-mm 先生 你现在不能退出你打电话 现在我们在里面
Mm-mm, mister, you can't back out now. You made that call, and now we're in it.
如果博尔顿想要打架 你最好让你的男孩准备战斗
If Bolton wants a fight, you better get your boys ready to fight.
嗯 更多的人会受伤
Well, more people are gonna get hurt.
你听你的女儿 伦敦
You listen to your daughter, London.
她知道她在说什么
She knows what she's talkin' about.
拉屎
Shit.
他们让我们坐在这里不做一个goddamn的事情
They got us sittin' around here not doing a goddamn thing.
是啊 博尔顿可能像狗一样对待我们 但至少他付了我们
Yeah, Bolton may have treated us like dogs, but at least he paid us.
Psst
Psst.
Psst - 嗯？
Psst. - Hmm?
- 过来
- Come here.
你想去转身吗？
You wanna have a go round?
- 什么？
- What?
我会让你做任何你想要的一罐沙丁鱼
I'll let you do anything you want for a can of sardines.
这是任何罢工的最难的部分
It's the hardest part of any strike,
当双方都挖出来 两边都不会发芽
when both sides are dug in and neither side's gonna budge.
H是穿在你身上的那个
H's the waitin' that wears on you.
士气降临 人们要离开
Morale's gonna drop, guys are gonna want to leave.
我们需要您的帮助保持你的眼睛
We're gonna need your help. Keep your eyes open.
一个错误的步骤和整个事情会分开
One false step and the whole damn thing will fall apart.
我不能保持喂养'我的女孩nothin' 但豆
I can't keep feedin' my girl nothin' but beans.
- 妈妈 我饿了 妈妈
- Mommy, I'm hungry, Mommy.
现在没有足够的毯子 所有这些人在营地
There ain't enough blankets now that there's all these people in camp.
我明白我们在路上得到更多的食物 毯子和用品
I understand. We got more food, blankets, and supplies on the way.
别担心 保持这个安静 但我在城里
Don't worry. Keep this quiet, but I was in town,
我听到几个谈话
I heard a few fellas talkin'.
他们说有更多的疤痕在卡车载入
They said there's more scabs comin' in by the truckload.
这些人都在他们的口袋里拿到枪和催泪弹
And these guys all got guns and tear gas bombs in their pockets.
这是一个谎言他们总是开始这样的谣言 滋生麻烦
That's a lie. They always start rumors like that to stir up trouble.
- 你还听到了什么？ - 我听说我们在这个营里有红军
- What else you heard? - I heard we got Reds in this camp.
共产党人
Communists.
你听到的是红色的？
Who you hear's a Red?
我们真正了解的家伙runnin这个东西？
What do we really know about the guys runnin' this thing?
好吧 你是一个真正的偏执狂fella 不是吗？
All right, you're a real paranoid fella, aren't you'?
你知道什么真正坚持我的爬行？
You know what really sticks in my craw'?
那次伦敦会议 好吗？
That meeting London took, okay?
现在 你看 这个罢工会结算
Now, you watch, this strike's gonna settle
和老伦敦将被驱逐一辆新车
and old London'll be drivin' a new car.
好吧 男孩 你闭上嘴 好吗？
All right, boy, you shut your mouth, all right'?
伦敦不是老鼠 任何人谁说 否则必须处理我
London ain't a rat, any of you who says otherwise has to deal with me.
- 坚韧
- Tough.
嘿 让你的手离开我 我会敲你的头
Hey, get your hands off me, I'll bash your head in.
我会砸你的头离开我们的营地！
I will bash your head in. Get out of our camp!
马上！走出我们的阵营！
Right now! Get out of our camp!
我不想看到你的脸这次会议结束了
I don't want to see your face. This meeting's over.
走！
Go!
去吧
Just go.
- 我能问你一件事吗？
- Can I ask you something?
- 拍摄
- Shoot.
你把那个梯子装好了 丹会落下吗？
Did you rig that ladder so Dan would fall?
- 我想你知道答案
- I think you know the answer.
- 我想听听你说
- I want to hear you say it.
- 好
- Fine.
我破坏了那个梯子
I sabotaged that ladder.
该死的你你直到地狱 Mac
Damn you. Damn you straight to hell, Mac.
那个可怜的老混蛋
That poor old bastard.
这些家伙每天在他们的生活得到螺丝
These guys get the screws put to them every day of their lives.
他们不会不在乎
They don't do nothin' about it.
但是 一旦一个老家伙从一个垃圾梯落下
But as soon as some old guy falls off a crap ladder,
他们愿意接受世界
they're willing to take on the world.
你想进来这是工作！
You wanted in. This is the job!
这是工作！
This is the job!
-  Joy怎么样？
- What about Joy?
- 喜悦是我的朋友
- Joy was my friend.
我没有让他起来
I didn't set him up.
但别人可能有 我们身边的人
But someone else may have, someone on our side.
- 也许
- Maybe.
我不知道
I don't know.
它更好...它更好的是值得的 Mac
It better... It better all be worth it, Mac.
它是...更好的是所有值得的 - 更好
It be... it better all be worth it. - It better be.
不就是不
No. Just no.
这是一个可怕的想法绝对不
That's a terrible idea. Absolutely not.
面对事实 Mac一个 博尔顿的男人ID'd你和吉姆
Face the facts, Mac. One, Bolton's men have ID'd you and Jim
作为这东西的首领
as ringleaders of this thing.
我们已经知道我们在营地里有老鼠
We already know we've got rats in the camp.
二 男人都在褪色
Two, the men are fading.
当事情变得严重时 伦敦可能没有胃
London may not have the stomach for this when things get serious.
我们需要一些东西来保持东西
We need something to keep things going.
所以你想要吉姆采取秋天？
So... so you want Jim to take the fall?
他比这个阵营中的每个人都更有价值
He's more valuable than everyone in this camp combined.
- 这不是你的第一个牛仔
- This ain't your first rodeo.
你知道迟早他们会跟着你们两个来
You know that sooner or later they're gonna come after the two of you.
然后 当这种情况发生时 我们可以为我们的利益
Then, when that happens, we can tum it in our favor.
你为什么这样？
Why are you acting like this?
你是那个总是说这不是我们任何一个人的人
You're the one who's always saying this isn't about any one of us.
是所有的谈话？
Was that all talk?
- 嘿 给你带了一些汤
- Hey, brought you some soup.
- 哦
- Oh.
- 你看起来有点难过
- You look sad.
- 我想我只是累了
- I think I'm just tired.
记住 你是在告诉我这个地方的时间吗？
Remember that time you were telling me about that place?
你知道 你想住的农场吗？
You know, that farm you wanted to live on?
'会员？
'Member?
你能再告诉我吗？请？
Can you tell me again? Please?
- 嗯 好吧 让我们来看看
- Hmm, well, let's see.
我会有一只山羊和一头母牛
I'd have a goat and a cow.
- 是啊？ - 但只是每一个
- Yeah? - But just one of each,
或者他们太麻烦了
or else they're too much trouble.
我会...
And I'd have...
我会有一个石围栏沿着驱动器
I'd have a stone fence along the drive,
一棵柳树在前院 两个
a willow tree in the front yard, two of 'em.
我从来不知道我有多少孩子...
I never know how many kids I wanted...
所以我想我会找出来
so I guess I'll find out.
如果你在做你的工作 努力工作一半
If you work half as hard at doing your job
因为你在刺伤你的朋友在后面
as you do at stabbing your friends in the back,
我们甚至不会在这种情况
we wouldn't even be in this situation.
嘿 Mac！混蛋关闭整个死路
Hey, Mac! The bastard shut the whole damn road down.
伦敦在那里
London's down there.
这是怎么回事？
What's going on?
大家走到路上
Everyone to the road.
- 哦 - 伦敦需要我们！
- Oh. - London needs us!
-  Ahem
- Ahem.
来吧！
Come on!
我们走吧！
Let's go!
- 丽莎 我要走了对不起
- Lisa, I gotta go. I'm sorry.
- 嘘
- Shh.
封面你自己！
Cover yourselves up!
继续！
Keep going!
- 站在你的面前！来吧！
- Stand your ground! Come on!
继续！
Keep going!
回到营地！
Go back to camp!
我们走吧！
Let's go! Let's go!
只有一种方式通过路障
There is only one way to get through a barricade.
我们都一起去吧那就对了
We all go at it at once. That's right.
我们整个人 然后他们不能阻止我们
The whole bunch of us, and then they can't stop us.
对他们会敲我们中的一个或两个
Right? They'll knock one or two of us,
但我们肯定会通过
but we'll get through for sure.
我们没有他们得到了气体 俱乐部 枪支
We got nothin'. They got gas, clubs, guns.
我们不能用我们的手！
We can't fight that with our bare hands!
- 你让他们抢你
- You let them rob you,
你让他们打败你 你让他们射杀你
you let them beat you, you let them shoot you,
现在他们让你像老鼠一样被困住 你还是不会打架？
now they got you trapped like rats and you still won't fight?
我现在就回去吧！
I will go back there right now!
马上！现在 谁跟我在一起？
Right now! Now, who's with me?
- 啊 狗屎
- Aw, shit.
- 你们没有？
- None of you?
我尽力帮助你！
I try to help you!
我给你这么goddamn多！
I give you so goddamn much!
- 冷静下来 Mac - 来吧 Mac
- Calm down, Mac. - Come on, Mac.
你只是坐在那里！好吧
You just sit there! All right.
- 移动！移动！ - 好吧 好吧 好吧 Mac
- Move! Move! Move! - All right, all right, all right, Mac.
苹果电脑！苹果电脑！苹果电脑！ -  Move！移动！
Mac! Mac! Mac! - Move! Move!
- 上帝死了 Mac！上帝死了 让我们走吧 - 移动！
- God damn it, Mac! God damn it, let's go. - Move!
-  Move！移动！ - 平静下来
- Move! Move! - Calm the hell down.
来吧！
Come on!
- 他妈的
- God damn it.
好吧 我失去了我的头回到那里
All right, I lost my head back there.
我只是这么累了
I'm just so goddamn tired.
好吧 你得休息一下 Mac
Well, you gotta get some rest, Mac.
你没有在天里睡觉是的 我知道
You haven't slept in days. Yeah, I know,
但这不会帮助 好吗？
but that's not gonna help, all right?
这些家伙甚至不会为自己而战斗
These guys won't even fight for themselves.
我在战争中看到了那些人
I saw guys just like that in the war
用他们的双手穿过机枪巢
go through a machine gun nest with their bare hands.
这些人甚至不会接几个绿色代表
These guys won't even take on a few green deputies.
Mac 吹了一口气你醒来后会感觉更好
Mac, take a blow. You'll feel better when you wake up.
不 我不会觉得更好 因为我会在同样的痛苦的混乱醒来
No, I won't feel better because I'll wake up in the same goddamn mess.
如果我们没有在这条路上得到耗材 那么罢工就不会成功
The strike won't hold if we don't get supplies down that road, Mac.
-  Ya想我不知道吗？
- Ya think I don't know that?
为什么没有别人想出一个计划！
Why doesn't somebody else come up with a plan!
那个怎么样？
How about that?
- 那么 你说什么？
- So, what do you say?
嗯？
. Hmm?
- 你可以做到吗？
- Can you do it?
- 他会做吗？
- Is he gonna do it?
- 是的 他会做对 Vinnie？
- Yeah, he'll do it. Right, Vinnie?
是的 我会做 但我只是不想看到任何人受伤
Yeah, I'll do it, but I just don't want to see anybody get hurt.
你关心那些红色混蛋怎么样？
What do you care about those Red bastards?
是啊 你说得对他们在一开始就说了一个大游戏
Yeah, you're right. They talked a big game in the beginning,
但我来这里工作 不玩政治
but I came here to work, not play politics.
嘿 Vinnie 我不...我不认为这是一个好主意
Hey, Vinnie, I don't... I don't think this is such a good idea.
嘿 - 没关系
Hey. - It's all right.
- 嘿 看 我知道一个家伙
- Hey, look, I know a guy.
他可以给你一份工作 这是一个很好的工作
He can get you a job, and it's a good job.
但首先你得把我们的钱放在你的嘴
But first you gotta put our money where your mouth is.
好吧 你说你会为我做任何事情
Well, you said you'd do anything for me.
不是吗？
Didn't you?
我不知道你们 当我报名参加
I don't know about you guys, when I signed up for this,
我以为我们会有一些结果！
I thought we was gonna have some results!
不只是在这里
Not just campin' out here,
starvin“像一群囚犯一样死亡！
starvin' to death like a bunch of prisoners!
我很害怕它！
I'm goddamn sick of it!
任何人都不会伤害这个？
Anybody else goddamn sick of this?
是啊！
Yeah!
看那个家伙
Look at that guy down there.
这是开始这一切的人 我是对的？
That's the guy that started all this, am I right'?
是啊 - 这里发生了什么？
Yeah. - What's going on here?
他强迫我们罢工 然后坐在他的帐篷里 吃了罐头桃子
He forced us to strike and then sat in his tent and ate canned peaches
而我们变湿了 生活了垃圾 猪不会碰
while we got wet and lived off garbage a pig wouldn't touch.
- 你说什么 伯克？ - 我们都知道你做的交易
- What the hell you talkin' about, Burke? - We all know about the deal you made.
不要试图否认它我们知道你只是做
Don't try to deny it. We know you'd just do
无论你的那个小女孩说什么
whatever that little girl of yours says.
她让你缠在她的小手指这么紧...
She's got you wrapped around her little finger so tight...
其他人？好吧 来吧 然后！
Anybody else? Well, come on, then!
- 嘿！ - 前进！
- Hey! - Go ahead!
还有谁想说我双交叉？好吧 去吧！
Who else wants to say I double crossed 'em? Well, go ahead!
- 这是不对的
- It ain't right.
还有人想对我的家人说些什么吗？
Anybody else want to say something about my family?
这是不对的这是不对的
That ain't right. That ain't right.
这不对！
That ain't right!
你在干什么？
What you doin' about it?
嘿 你不满意这次罢工怎么样？
Hey, you ain't happy with how this strike is going?
没有！ - 你想改变吗？
No! - You want to change that'?
是的 - 你必须为此而战 上帝死了
Yes! - You have to fight for that, God damn it.
好吧 因为男人喜欢
All right, 'cause men like that,
他们试图把我们分开
they're trying to tear us apart
他们试图让我们回来
They're trying to hold us back.
不再不再！
No more. No more!
不再！不再！
No more! No more!
等待的时间完成！是啊！
The time for waiting is done! Yeah!
他们认为他们可以像小猪一样给我们打电话我们是猪吗？
They think they can just pen us in like little pigs. Are we pigs'?
没有！
No!
- 不！你对这个人生气 伦敦？
- No! You're angry at this man, London?
嗯 他会用手露出那些路障 如果必要的话
Well, he's gonna go smash those barricades with his bare hands, if necessary.
- 你是对的
- You're damn right.
- 我们要得到那辆卡车
- We're gonna get that truck
我们要通过'em！
and we're gonna drive it right through 'em!
是的 你想驾驶那辆卡车通过？
Yeah, you wanna drive that truck right through?
是啊！
Yeah!
我们是猪吗？没有！
Are we pigs? No!
我们要战斗吗？是啊！
Are we gonna fight? Yeah!
- 弗兰克 拿出司机
- Frank, take out the driver.
拿出司机 弗兰克！带他出去！
Take out the driver, Frank! Take him out!
带他出去！
Take him out!
我们说我们要穿过那个路障 我们做了什么？
We said we were gonna come through that barricade, and what did we do?
我们经过那个路障！
We went through that barricade!
每个人都离开 在街垒射击
Everyone left to get shot at the barricade.
- 是的
- Yeah.
- 他不会停止哭泣 - 嘿
- He won't stop crying. - Hey.
我的奶奶曾经这样做
My grandma used to do this.
Ahem 这里
Ahem, here.
你去了
There you go.
他需要一个父亲
He's gonna need a father.
我要求吉姆和我一起建房子
I was gonna ask Jim to build a house with me
当这一切都结束了
when this is all over with.
我以为他会做一个好父亲
I thought he'd make a good father.
- 好...
- Well...
这是不会发生的
that ain't gonna happen.
孩子现在发烧了
Kid's got the fever now.
他会留在这东西 直到他被逮捕或射杀 不是吗？
He's gonna stay at this thing until he's arrested or shot, isn't he?
- 他是一个艰难的孩子
- He's a tough kid.
他会没事的
He'll be all right.
- 你会像你一样把他变冷吗？
- Are you gonna turn him cold like you?
- 丽莎
- Lisa.
吉姆
Jim.
拉屎
Shit.
嘿 吉米！
Hey, Jimmy!
我们开始做吧！我们开始做吧！
Let's do it! Let's do it!
- 吉姆！
- Jim!
吉姆
Jim.
抱歉
Sorry.
我知道你对她很甜这不是她 是我
I knew you were sweet on her. It's not her, it's me.
只是这么goddamn孤独 我认为一点温暖会有所帮助
Just so goddamn lonely, I thought a little warmth would help.
- 没关系 她不是我的女孩
- It's okay, she's not my girl.
这不行
It's not okay.
我是一个自私的ch子 我知道
I'm a selfish son of a bitch, and I know it.
Mac 没关系我欣赏的教训谢谢
Mac, it's okay. I appreciate the lesson. Thank you.
- 教训？什么教训？
- Lesson? What lesson?
好吧 你总是告诉我 没有时间或地方的likin'人
Well, you always told me that there's no time or place for likin' people,
并感谢你帮助我看到这一点
and thank you for helping me see that.
她只是一个女孩她不重要工作的重要性
She's just a girl. She's not important. The job's what matters.
好的-
. Okay-
现在我有工作要做
Now I got work to do.
Turnin'成一个适当的ch子的儿子 不是吗？
Turnin' into a proper son of a bitch, ain't ya?
- 就像你教我一样
- Just like you taught me.
- 吉姆？
- Jim?
你不知道我在乎你吗？
Don't you know I care about you?
- 是的
- Yeah.
有趣的方式showin'它
Funny way of showin' it.
- 对不起我被吓到了
- I'm sorry. I was scared.
- 你害怕什么？
- What were you scared of?
- 所有这一切
- Of all of this.
我害怕我也会失去你
I was scared I was gonna lose you too.
- 你从来没有我
- You never had me.
我在这里为事业
I'm here for the cause.
嘘 保持你的声音
Hush, keep your voices down-.
- 告诉我你有什么 乡下男孩
- Show me what you got, country boy.
- 这只是这一回事
- It's just this one thing.
-  Vinnie 我真的不想这样做
- Vinnie, I really don't want to do this.
时间的浪费'我们走吧
Time's wastin'. Let's go.
- 警卫怎么样？
- What about the guard?
- 你不担心他
- Don't you worry about him.
这才是我的姑娘
That's my girl.
Hey-
. Hey-
呃 我应该告诉你 那个大家伙 呃 伦敦？
Uh, I was supposed to tell you, the big guy, uh, London'?
他想要你回到营地
He wants you back at camp.
Nah 他让我整夜留下来
Nah, he asked me to stay on all night.
- 这是他告诉我的
- That's what he told me.
-  Vinnie 我真的不想这样做 - 安静
- Vinnie, I really don't want to do this. - Quiet.
拿着它
Take this.
以防万一
Just in case.
- 什么？ - 你不必使用它
- What? - You don't have to use it.
只要注意一下
Just keep an eye out.
- 继续 - 狗屎 狗屎
- Go on. - Shit, shit.
- 停下来
- Stay down.
Vinnie ... Vinnie 我们真的不应该这样做
Vinnie... Vinnie, we really shouldn't be doing this.
- 你保持手表 好吗？
- You keep watch, all right?
好啦好啦
Come on, come on.
- 啊 耶稣上帝
- Aw, Jesus God.
哦 那些混蛋
Oh, those bastards.
- 啊 基督！
- Aw, Christ!
跑 你蠢的农场男孩！
Run, you stupid farm boy!
- 火！火！
- Fire! Fire!
有人！
Somebody!
火！
Fire!
- 凯勒 你老鼠！ - 伦敦 不 伦敦！
- Keller, you rat! - London, no, London!
- 你在哪里 男孩？ - 我在这里 我在这里
- Where were you, boy? - I was here, I was here,
但那时你送那个女孩来找我
but then you sent that girl to come and get me.
- 女孩？什么女孩？什么女孩？
- Girl? What girl'? What girl?
我不知道她是谁她只是一个女孩
I don't know who she was. She was just some girl.
当我到了这里 它已经开始
By the time I had got here, it already had started.
- 啊 耶稣！
- Aw, Jesus!
你得到一些人 你冲出他们的树林
You get some men and you flush out them woods,
你扫荡营地 你找出谁做了这个
you sweep the camp, you find out who did this.
去做现在 男孩！
Go do it now, boy!
好的
Okay. Anderson.
安德森
Anderson.
- 它在我们 Mac
- It's on us, Mac.
这是在我们
This is on us.
- 那天 当那件衣服来了
- That day, when that suit came,
你告诉他们 如果他们碰到那个老人？
what did you tell them if they touch that old man?
如果安德森给了这个词 我们将正式侵入
If Anderson gives the word, we'll be officially trespassing.
他们有理由打电话给国民警卫队
They'll have grounds to call in the National Guard.
你们都要坐在这里
You're all just gonna sit here
并等待他们为了给我们带来什么
and wait for whatever they have to bring down on us.
懦夫 懦夫 懦夫 懦夫
Coward, coward, coward, coward.
精细
Fine.
你认为你会去哪里？
Where the hell do you think you're going?
我不能忍受被哄骗在这里与你懦夫一分钟
I can't stand being cooped up in here with you cowards a minute longer.
我想烧掉那个整个山谷
I'd like to burn that whole goddamn valley down.
- 维拉 来吧 - 伦敦？
- Vera, come on. - London?
它是什么？
What is it?
我们抓到一个人偷偷摸摸
We caught a guy sneakin' around
在谷仓和营地后面
behind the barn and the camp.
他拿着枪 - 把他带到这里
He had a gun. - Bring him in here.
- 进入这里进入
- Get in here. Get in.
- 很好把他带到这里 - 当然 Mac
- Did good bringing him in here. - Sure thing, Mac.
我知道了
I got it.
我们让你在那里 他们会杀了你你懂的？
We let you out there, they're gonna kill you. You know that?
- 现在 谁派了你？ - 没有人
- Now, who sent you? - Nobody.
- 谁派你来的？
- Who sent you?!
我不知道 有一个孩子从村里送我出去
I don't know, some kid from the village sent me out.
- 谁？ - 我不知道 请
- Who? - I don't know, please.
这太... ...对不起 我不能这么做
This is too... I'm sorry, I can't be pan of this.
- 请
- Please.
- 我不能
- I can't.
我会做的
I'll do it.
- 请请 这就够了
- Please. Please, it's enough.
请
Please.
哦 我的宝贝！
Oh, my baby!
- 请！
- Please!
妈妈！
Mommy!
嘿-
Hey-
- 我走进城里 把你打开了
- I went into town and turned you in.
警长会把你的全部踢在我的土地上
Sheriff's gonna kick the whole lot of you off my land.
- 我只是想说对不起
- I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
我们不希望这种情况发生
We didn't want this to happen.
- 你知道你的问题是什么？
- You know what your problem is?
你从来没有任何东西
You never own anything.
你从来没有种植任何树 看着'
You never planted any trees, watched 'em grow,
用你自己的手触摸
touched 'em with your own hands.
你混蛋从来没有拥有任何东西
You bastards never owned anything.
你从来没有把你的手放在你自己的泥土！
You never put your hands in your own dirt!
在尊重 我们从来没有机会没有什么
With respect, we never had a chance to own nothing.
是的 我听了你的承诺
Yeah, I listened to all your promises.
现在整个作物烧了
Now the whole crop's burnt up,
只是一个时间的问题 银行把这一切
just a matter of time before the bank takes it all.
- 指针？
- The pointers?
狗是好吗？ - 你怎么看？
Are the dogs all right? - What do you think?
狗舍在谷仓的中间拍打
Kennel was slap in the middle of the barn.
我们收到了一个侵权投诉
We have received a trespassing complaint
从这块土地的所有者
from the owner of this land.
总督一直没有追索权
The governor has been left with no recourse
但打电话给国民警卫队
but to call in the National Guard.
我们将通过这个营在明天日出
We will be comin' through this camp at sunrise tomorrow,
与200枪和10多卡车就像这一个
with 200 guns and 10 more trucks just like this one.
剩余的任何人将被强行删除
Anyone remaining will be forcibly removed.
任何抵抗都会得到满足
Any resistance will be met
具有迅速和永久的力量
with swift and permanent force.
- 只是减速 减速
- Just slow down, slow down.
所有的 只是慢下来他们的枪
All y'all, just slow down with them guns.
只是因为你有一个非法侵入
Just because you have a trespassin' charge
不要给你没有权利成为射击球员
don't give none of ya the right to be shootin' guys.
对是啊！
Right. Yeah!
- 好吧 现在你是对的
- Well, now you're right about that.
但煽动暴力
But incitement of violence,
破坏私人财产
destruction of private property,
破坏 暴乱 抵制逮捕和谋杀？
vandalism, rioting, resisting arrest, and murder?
好吧 现在 这是另一个问题
Well, now, that's another question entirely.
谋杀'？只有杀人犯在这里是由博尔顿和他的家伙
Murder'? Only murderin' done here is by Bolton and his guys.
- 哦！ - 不是我们！不是我们！
- Oh! - Not us! Not us!
昨晚 一个男人的家被烧在地上
Last night, a man's home was burned to the ground.
他的儿子在那火中死了
His son died in that fire.
你把这个暴行负责的人
You turn in the man responsible for this atrocity,
除此以外
otherwise,
我们会考虑
we will consider
每一个人
each and every one of you
成为这一罪行的共犯
to be an accomplice to this crime.
你没有证据 我们有任何与此有关
You got no proof that any of us had anything to do with that.
你忘恩负义的小shitheels！
You ungrateful little shitheels!
我们给你工作 你把它扔在我们的脸上
We gave you work, you threw it in our face.
我们让你在政治
We let you play at politics,
parleyed与你像商人
parleyed with you like businessmen,
你怎么回应？
and how do you respond?
无端 肆意破坏！
Unprovoked, wanton destruction!
博尔顿 这是一个谎言！不 闭嘴！
Bolton, that's a lie! No, shut up!
- 这是一个goddamn谎言！ - 闭嘴！
- That's a goddamn lie! - Shut up!
这个游戏结束了
This game is over. Get out.
- 黎明 先生们
- Daybreak, gentlemen.
- 好吧 来吧我们走吧
- All right, come on. Let's go.
哦 来 伦敦他疯了 你看不到吗？
Oh, come on, London. He's bluffing, can't you see that'?
那条关于孩子的线被烧了
That line about the kid gettin' burned.
这只是一群公牛来摇我们
That's just a bunch of bull to shake us.
我不敢相信警长说的一个字
I can't believe one word that sheriff said.
我的意思是 那个孩子真的死了 它会在所有的文件
I mean, that kid really got killed, it woulda been in all the papers.
- 维拉？
- Vera?
- 当时太黑了
- It was dark.
很难看到很多东西
It's hard to see much of anything.
他们不断谈论他们所有的枪支和卡车
And they keep talkin' about all those guns and trucks that they have.
如果他们有所有这些枪和卡车
If they had all those guns and trucks,
他们不会谈论他们 他们只是滚动进来
they wouldn't talk about 'em, they'd just roll right in.
那个警长只是想让我们分散 所以我们不要打架
That sheriff's just trying to get us to scatter so we don't put up a fight.
- 他是说话吗 Mac？ - 他知道他在说什么
- Is he tellin' it straight, Mac? - He knows what he's talking about.
如果我们现在折叠 没有废品
If we fold right now, without a scrap,
我们所经历的一切都是一无所有
everything we've been through been for nothing.
我知道这是一个地狱的责任 伦敦 但来了
I know that's a hell of a responsibility, London, but come on.
如果他们发现维拉烧毁了那所房子...
If they find out that Vera burned down that house...
我们没有告诉她做任何事情
We didn't tell her to do anything.
不要用我 作为借口我完全知道我在做什么
Don't use me as an excuse. I knew full well what I was doin'.
这是我的决定不是你的 我的
This is my decision. Not yours, mine.
我们应该打它！我们应该吗？
Should we fight it out'! Should we?
这取决于你 伦敦
It's up to you, London.
你知道什么Mac和我的想法
You know what Mac and I think.
伦敦 你是老板的人 所以如果你想把它投票...
London, you're the boss man, so if you want to put it to a vote...
把它投票
put it to a vote.
我会和男孩说话我们将在今晚投票
I'll talk to the boys. We'll vote tonight.
得到你说的
Get what you're saying.
我们不知道它会是这样的
We didn't know it was gonna be like this.
我们得到了妇女我们有老人
We got women. We got old men.
我们不是军队我们不能赢得这场战斗
We aren't an army. We can't win this fight.
结束了
It's over.
这个山谷太有组织
This valley is too organized.
所有的财产由三个人拥有
All the property's owned by three men.
他们拥有银行 他们控制着法院
They own the banks, they control the courts.
你告诉我什么？
What'd you tell me once?
每次一个卫兵用刺刀刺入一个水果流浪汉
Every time a guardsman jabs a fruit tramp with a bayonet,
一千个人来到我们身边？
a thousand men come on our side?
如果我们打击这一点
If we fight this out,
全国都会知道
the whole country will know about it.
我们可以做一些真正的改变
We can make some real change.
我想让你走出这里
I want you to get outta here.
今晚
Tonight.
拿丽莎和宝宝去
Take Lisa and the baby and go.
保存自己另一场战斗
Save yourself for another fight.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
想要投票的人们出去！
People that want a vote go on out!
- 我们需要投票 - 让我们投票
- We need a vote. - Let's get a vote in.
我想投票！
I want to vote!
你怎么这么温暖？
How's it that you're always so warm?
也许你只是这么冷
Maybe you're just so cold.
我应得的
I deserve that.
我不知道今晚会发生什么 我只想说...
I don't know what's gonna happen tonight, I just want to say that...
然后不要
Then don't.
我不会试图去争论
I'm not gonna try and argue out of fightin'.
因为我知道你不会听所以在这种情况下 不要说什么
'Cause I know you won't listen. So in that case, don't say anything.
我今年已经失去了一个人我不能再做
I've already lost one man this year. I can't do it again.
我只是不想让我们之间的东西这种方式
I just don't want to leave things between us this way.
- 嘘
- Shh.
- 我可以抱他吗？
- Can I hold him?
嘘嘘
Shh. Shh.
嘘 不要哭
Shh, don't cry.
不要哭 不要哭 不要哭
Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry.
他停止哭泣
He stopped crying.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
记住农场
Remember that farm
与狗 牛和山羊？
with the dog, cow, and the goats?
有我在那里的地方吗？
Is there a spot for me there?
是...
Yes...
在另一个生活
in another life.
- 吉姆！ - 是啊？
- Jim! - Yeah?
有一个家伙在果园里躺在沟里
There's some guy over in the orchard lying in a ditch.
他伤害了真正的坏我认为这是医生
He's hurt real bad. I think it's the doctor.
- 谁？文伯顿？ - 是的他说他需要你
- Who? Doc Burton? - Yeah. He said he needs you.
' Mac？
', Mac?
Mac 文档还在这里 但他伤害了真正的坏
Mac, the doc's still here, but he's hurt real bad.
- 根据谁？ - 有孩子告诉我
- According to who? - Some kid told me.
他在果园里来吧 让我们走吧
He's over in the orchard. Come on, let's go.
好吧 我会...
All right, I'll...
我会去 好吧？你留在这里
I'll go, all right? You stay here.
不 你在说什么？我们都是goin'
No, what are you talkin' about? We're both goin'.
Edie现在需要你
Edie needs you right now.
-  Edie需要我吗？你在说什么...  - 吉姆！
- Edie needs me? What are you talk... - Jim!
你为什么要听我的话 因为基督的缘故？
Will you just listen to me, for Christ's sake?
只是去看她 好吗？
Just go see her, okay?
你会听我吗？
Will you just listen to me?
好 我会去爱迪
Fine, I'll go get Edie.
你去得Doc 好吧？ - 是的
You go get Doc, all right? - Yeah.
Edie？
Edie?
- 吉姆 -  Mac说你需要我
- Jim. - Mac said you need me.
呃 当然咯 他在哪里？
Oh... uh, he did. Yeah, of course. Where is he?
好吧 有些孩子进来 说文档受伤了
Well, some kid came in and said the doc was hurt,
在果园里我要去找他
in the orchard. And I was gonna go get him,
但后来Mac说你需要我
but then Mac said that you needed me,
所以他就去找他
so then he went to find him.
他妈的
God damn it.
这是一个设置
It's a set-up.
- 听 吉姆 - 这是给我的
- Listen, Jim. - It was meant for me.
吉姆...？吉姆！
Jim...? Jim!
吉姆 离开吧！
Jim, leave 'em be!
苹果电脑！苹果电脑！
. Mac! Mac!
一天一美元比这些人杀了更好
A dollar a day is better than gettin' these people killed.
你不能每天靠一美元生活
You can't live on a dollar a day.
'Mac！
' Mac!
苹果电脑！
Mac!
你看到今天有什么下来
You saw what was down there today.
不要只是坐在这里和对方争论我明白...
Don't just sit here and argue with each other. I understand...
我说每天三美元！
I say three dollars a day!
- 你看到了发生了什么！ - 我不知道 也许这是对的
- You saw what happened! - I don't know, maybe that's right.
听 人们 不要只是坐在这里 互相争辩
Listen, folks, don't just sit here and argue with each other.
我明白...
I understand...
我们必须战斗！我们不能赢得这个东西！
We've got to fight! We can't win this thing!
嘿！
Hey!
嘿！嘿！
Hey! Hey!
- 男孩 挂一秒这是吉姆！ -  argue argue argue ...
- Boys, hang on a second. That's Jim! - Argue, argue, argue...
他们射杀了他！
They shot him!
他死了
He's dead.
哦 Mac苹果电脑
Oh, Mac. Mac.
他的名字...
His name...
是MacLeod
was MacLeod.
你都知道他是Mac？
You all knew him as Mac?
苹果电脑！
Mac!
他是你的一个
He was one of you.
他战斗
He fought,
他为你而战
and he fought for you.
他从来不想要任何回报
And he never wanted anything in return.
他给你的生命
He gave his life for you.
他给了他的生命
And he gave his life
因为比你大的原因
for a cause bigger than you.
想法
For an idea.
主意...
The idea...
那些人喜欢你
that guys like you,
和我喜欢的人...
and guys like me...
应有尊严
deserve dignity,
并应得到尊重
and deserve respect,
并应该公平地分享我们用双手做的
and deserve a fair share of what we make with our bare hands.
苹果电脑！
Mac!
那些混蛋...
And those bastards...
他们射杀了他
they shot him.
苹果电脑！
Mac!
苹果电脑！苹果电脑！
Mac! Mac!
他们射杀了他...
They shot him...
相信自己比自己更大
for believing in somethin' bigger than himself.
他们射杀了他
And they shot him,
因为现在 他们认为...
because now, they think...
我们都会整理起来回家
that we'll all shrivel up and go home
像一群温顺的狗
like a bunch of meek dogs.
但我们不会这样做
But we ain't gonna do that.
我们是猪吗？没有
No. Are we pigs? No.
ATS我们猪？没有！
ATS we pigs? No!
随你便我们放弃了吗？
It's up to you. Do we give up?
- 不！ - 我们让他们赢了吗？
- No! - Do we let them win?
- 不！ - 或者我们站在这里 打架？
- No! - Or do we stand here, and fight?
斗争！ - 战斗！
Fight! - Fight!
“战斗！ - 战斗:
" Fight! - Fight:
斗争！
Fight! ; Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
斗争！
Fight! Fight! Fight!
人们认为他们想要财富或权力
People think they want wealth or power,
但这不是它
but that ain't it.
人们只是想知道他们的生活很重要...
People just wanna know their lives matter...
它们很重要
That they matter.
对自己的生活有一些控制
Having some control over your own life.
这是值得争取的
That's worth fighting for,
无论成本
no matter the cost.
来吧 你们都是好工人
Come, all of you good workers
我会告诉你的好消息
Good news to you I'll tell
如何善良的旧联合
Of how the good old union
来到这里停留
Has come in here to dwell
你在哪边？
Which side are you on?
我的爸爸是矿工
My daddy was a miner
我是矿工的儿子
And I'm a miner's son
我会坚持联盟
And I'll stick with the union
直到每场战斗的胜利
Till every battle's won
你在哪边？
Which side are you on?
来吧 你们都是好工人
Come, all of you good workers
我会告诉你的好消息
Good news to you I'll tell
如何善良的旧联合
Of how the good old union
来到这里停留
Has come in here to dwell
你在哪边？
Which side are you on?
我的爸爸是矿工
My daddy was a miner
我是矿工的儿子
And I'm a miner's son
我会坚持联盟
And I'll stick with the union
直到每场战斗的胜利
Till every battle's won
你在哪边？
Which side are you on?
他们在哈兰县说话
They say in Harlan County
没有中立的
There are no neutral there
您是联盟人
You'll either be a union man
Or a thug for J. H. Blair
你在哪边？
Which side are you on?
哦 工人 你能忍受吗？
Oh, workers, can you stand it?
哦 告诉我怎么办？
Oh, tell me how you can?
你会是一个恶心的疤吗？
Will you be a lousy scab?
还是你会成为一个男人吗？
Or will you be a man?
你在哪边？
Which side are you on?
不要欺骗老板
Don't scab for the bosses
不要听他们的谎言
Don't listen to their lies
我们贫困的人没有 有机会
Us poor folks haven't got a chance
除非我们组织
Unless we organize
你在哪边？
Which side are you on?